<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>UX on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</title>
    <link>https://socalranch.land/tags/ux/</link>
    <description>Recent content in UX on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2011 10:04:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://socalranch.land/tags/ux/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Good Choice To Lose</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-12-23-a-good-choice-to-lose/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2011 10:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-12-23-a-good-choice-to-lose/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Since I had some issues that affected my productivity with google applications in Chrome I re-configured my system to use native apps for chat, mail and calendar. Overall I like the changes and the trade off is worth it since I do not have to log into my google account 30 times a day. I miss using one browser (especially with the three finger swipe down that shows me all of my tabs) but I still use it for development and other browsing. Seriously I counted the last day and it was 30 times google asked me to log in in chrome so I don&amp;#8217;t mind having all my apps in one place. Oddly, firefox and safari do not have this incessant logging in to google services issue with google services. Weird, I know. But I think I&amp;#8217;ll stick with Safari for my work apps accounts for now and use the native apps with personal accounts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This leads me to my point. I was restoring some music to my itunes library and when I dragged and dropped it onto the itunes application I noticed that instead of asking me to choose and drag to Music or Movies, etc; it just highlighted the&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flow</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-02-04-flow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 08:57:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-02-04-flow/</guid>
      <description>As I work through the additions I realized what bothers me about the cms. It gets in the way of my flow. I can&amp;#8217;t just do a bunch of things and then save them. I have to do one thing, wait for the blocking ajax call. I thought the point of ajax was to let the user do other stuff while the service worked in the background.
The system should be able to track where the user was and be able to quickly, )one click) get them back there.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>