<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>UI/UX on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</title>
    <link>https://socalranch.land/categories/ui/ux/</link>
    <description>Recent content in UI/UX on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2015 19:41:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://socalranch.land/categories/ui/ux/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Modifying Phone Links For Screens</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2015-12-15-modifying-phone-links-for-screens/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2015 19:41:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2015-12-15-modifying-phone-links-for-screens/</guid>
      <description>Your Problem So you have a link thats a phone number. You have this because you want the link to auto dial when on a phone but look like text and not have any functionality when on a screen larger than a phone. As an engineer you don&amp;#8217;t want to duplicate html to provide this feature and would love if css had a way to encapsulate this on one place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motion Excitement</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-09-05-motion-excitement/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2014 14:54:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-09-05-motion-excitement/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#8217;m following the progress of Zurb&amp;#8217;s Foundation For Apps. They have published some ideas related to erasing the difference between native mobile apps and web apps on a mobile device.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Note To Self</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-06-22-note-to-self/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2014 00:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-06-22-note-to-self/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Or, career plans for the next two decades:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“One of the main ways to deliver education over the next 10 to 20 years is going to be through smartphones,” von Ahn says.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keep In Mind</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-06-02-keep-in-mind/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 16:13:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-06-02-keep-in-mind/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There are guidelines to everything under the sun. Getting what you want, where you want, how you want is just another process that we all go through. It can always be done differently but the savvy folks learn to look at the lessons learned by those who traveled before them and apply their lessons appropriately. These are guidelines. With that said, Keep these in mind when you are designing your path:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remember The Terminal</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-05-21-the-terminal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2014 15:26:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-05-21-the-terminal/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/Screen-Shot-2014-05-21-at-8.18.14-AM.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;alignleft size-medium wp-image-5902&#34; src=&#34;http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/Screen-Shot-2014-05-21-at-8.18.14-AM-300x38.png&#34; alt=&#34;Screen Shot 2014-05-21 at 8.18.14 AM&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;38&#34; srcset=&#34;http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/Screen-Shot-2014-05-21-at-8.18.14-AM-300x38.png 300w, http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/Screen-Shot-2014-05-21-at-8.18.14-AM.png 554w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#8217;ll forget it when your app does the same things, in the same way and is as easily customizable as the command line.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thing As Interface</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-03-10-thing-as-interface/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 14:07:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-03-10-thing-as-interface/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have been thinking about why I don&amp;#8217;t want my apps to make me think. I&amp;#8217;m there to do a job and move on. If I have to change this, fix that or connect to the network because the app forgot that it just got the data for this screen a minute ago before I switched apps to check my calendar; then the app is making me do more mental work than I budgeted for the task.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Think For Me</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-08-15-think-for-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2013 15:55:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-08-15-think-for-me/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was using &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.atlassian.com/software/jira&#34;&gt;JIRA&lt;/a&gt; this morning and it tried to think for me. A few months ago we switched to JIRA issue tracking at work. ANd it is miles ahead of the disjointed system we were using before. Still, it tried to think for me to make things easier I assume. It didn&amp;#8217;t get it right and ended up leading me down a path that caused me to re-do about five minutes of working.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swipe to Action</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-08-02-swipe-to-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2013 12:38:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-08-02-swipe-to-action/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a style=&#34;line-height: 1.6;&#34; href=&#34;http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2013/08/20130802-113456.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;alignnone size-full&#34; alt=&#34;20130802-113456.jpg&#34; src=&#34;http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2013/08/20130802-113456.jpg&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future Actions ( in your computer interface )</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-07-28-future-actions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2013 23:13:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-07-28-future-actions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The next user interface will combine motion with action. Most of the &amp;#8216;action&amp;#8217; will be spoken in the way an executive gives orders to the minions. Copy this, save that and put the other thing over there, oh yeah, when I finish this, remind me to do the other thing before I get distracted by shinty Internet things. All desired actions will  be spoken aloud in conversation. You know people like me whom in the middle of a problem talk it through. Yeah, these additions to ourinterface will be great for us. 🙂&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Side Tracks</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-03-08-side-tracks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2013 22:59:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-03-08-side-tracks/</guid>
      <description>I was writing something else when I got sidetracked with this irony. I had to say it out loud to realize what was wrong here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Stones</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-02-20-digital-stones/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2013 22:02:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-02-20-digital-stones/</guid>
      <description>Teaching Hannah how to run her iPod touch was easy, I just had to play with the settings and shines noises. Then when I take a picture of it, she tells me to wait. And she asks me how to resign the keyboard from the screen.
So when she steps on her first digital stones and wants to move them around, i can only smile and agree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Tree Software</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-12-31-happy-tree-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 23:42:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-12-31-happy-tree-software/</guid>
      <description>Project goals for 2013: the year of the happy tree.
 Pinboard appfor iOS with collections view Tree &amp;amp; Leaf generation software</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UX Matters: Why Hangouts needs to be more like FaceTime</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-12-25-ux-matters-why-hangouts-needs-to-be-more-like-facetime/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2012 12:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-12-25-ux-matters-why-hangouts-needs-to-be-more-like-facetime/</guid>
      <description>Tried to set up a Hangout for family in different states. For regular users of google plus not an issue. For users who logged in a while ago and set everything up just after the service went public not so much. Here is what I noticed on Christmas AM while trying to help them and watch my daughter open her gifts from Santa.
 Plugins are horrible for ux &amp;#8211; that&amp;#8217;s why we just had them revert to FaceTime, it never asks you to install anything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The New Slideshow</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-03-08-the-new-slideshow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2012 21:03:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-03-08-the-new-slideshow/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have come across several neat JavaScript programs that take advantage of all the CSS3 fun you can do in modern browsers. Each time I see a new one idas go racing through my head. I can do this or that or &amp;#8230;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A couple weeks ago I got one of those mailer brochures from a credit card company with pretty images and pithy tag lines telling me all about their product. I don&amp;#8217;t need any more credit cards right now. But it did get me thinking, how could I do this on a webpage? So I marked it up with one of Hannah&amp;#8217;s pens into some simple markup for the different pieces on each page and put it on my desk. Then I cleaned the office and tossed it. However, the idea continued to roll around in my head and about a week later I finished reading &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.thestartupofyou.com/&#34;&gt;The Start Up Of You&lt;/a&gt;. I joined the group on LinkedIn. Why not, I have been spending quite a bit of time on there looking for reasonable jobs lately. So it was easy to join and nice to come across variations of ideas in the book as well as intelligent discussion about how to&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post Solo Followup</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-07-11-post-solo-followup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2011 19:19:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-07-11-post-solo-followup/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the tradition of reviewing my &amp;#8216;performace&amp;#8217; I hit the big items on my list here: &lt;a href=&#34;http://hippeelee.com/blog/2011/07/the-solo-week/&#34; title=&#34;The Solo Week&#34;&gt;http://hippeelee.com/blog/2011/07/the-solo-week/&lt;/a&gt;. I didn&amp;#8217;t get to climb but everything else got the attention it needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some notes for the future. Staining is messy. I&amp;#8217;ll need to pressure wash the windows and deck furniture &amp;#8230; the wind blew it everywhere. The wood looks good though and i&amp;#8217;ll touch up on a cool day this fall. The Wall is built but I need one more big block and then three or four more toppers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No pictures, I think I may switch to Google+ picture albums and just link to them here. A social network is not really the place for these kinds of posts but the picture manager I am using isn&amp;#8217;t as slick as the plus picture interface. Speaking of plus &amp;#8211; the coolest thing was supper easy. I got an email notification from the Erie, CO website for a police alert. It seems that 7 homes were bergled over the weekend and it was quick and easy to share that and target only the people who would be interested in it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More and more, what I like, is a well thought out UI/UX. From looking at things that break&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Child Shapes</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-01-06-simple-child-shapes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2011 15:05:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-01-06-simple-child-shapes/</guid>
      <description>Here is my vision for the css3zen design. The theme is simple child shapes, blocks, circles, triangles and rectangles &amp;#8211; The first shapes that Hannah recognized. Since there is a child element we will keep the colors to primary (but you can use transparency if needed).
The layout will be simple, blocky and make use of whitespace. The imagry will incorporate the shapes theme and I&amp;#8217;ll use gimp to create them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CMS Thoughts</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-12-15-cms-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2010 23:20:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-12-15-cms-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>When I ran my site with WordPress there were a few things that bugged me but I didn&amp;#8217;t get to far beyond theming for it to really matter. It was easy to install, easy to configure and easy to use. And, it just worked. While I didn&amp;#8217;t enjoy all of the upgrading things I had to do, that was partly because I chose to run it on a personal server. Now that I am on their platform most of that pain has gone away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&amp;#8217;s Complicated</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-12-09-its-complicated/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 17:23:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-12-09-its-complicated/</guid>
      <description>I received a 32 page power point presentation for a simple how-to do something in a web application. If it takes 32 steps to do something (simple) then the application is to complicated.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>