<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Snowboarding on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</title>
    <link>https://socalranch.land/tags/snowboarding/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Snowboarding on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 08:57:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://socalranch.land/tags/snowboarding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Flow</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-02-04-flow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 08:57:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-02-04-flow/</guid>
      <description>As I work through the additions I realized what bothers me about the cms. It gets in the way of my flow. I can&amp;#8217;t just do a bunch of things and then save them. I have to do one thing, wait for the blocking ajax call. I thought the point of ajax was to let the user do other stuff while the service worked in the background.
The system should be able to track where the user was and be able to quickly, )one click) get them back there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Epic Powder Day</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-12-22-epic-powder-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2010 08:37:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-12-22-epic-powder-day/</guid>
      <description>It was most certainly out of the ordinary. And she wanted to go faster while yelling at me to let her do it on her own 🙂
It was almost as much work as riding the park and the pipe or carving out heelside turns that compliment the toeside. It was more fun than I have ever had on the slopes and I returned home a very proud papa.
At least equal to being hip deep in powder on a double black diamond above the treeline and more fulfilling than turning my first frontside 360.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowboarding and Strategy</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-11-21-snowboarding-and-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2010 04:21:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-11-21-snowboarding-and-strategy/</guid>
      <description>I put my bindings on the new snowboard. It&amp;#8217;s light! I think. I have big plans for the t6.
Hannah is getting smart, strategic almost. She asks set up questions anticipating what my answer will be. Then she follows up with what she really wants.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>