<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gurgi on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</title>
    <link>https://socalranch.land/tags/gurgi/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gurgi on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2011 12:45:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://socalranch.land/tags/gurgi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Gurgi&amp;#8217;s Last Day</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-10-16-gurgis-last-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2011 12:45:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-10-16-gurgis-last-day/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It was a cool crisp fall day. The storms of the day before had moved of to the east. We got up early with the sunrise and had a simple breakfast. Toast for me and scrambled eggs, turkey bacon and grilled chicken for you. Sitting around is never good for the soul so we went out to Mr BoBo. Hannah rode in the arena and you and Whitney chased him for a bit, like you always do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We came back home and I took care of a few things around the house. Once I got done I joined you and Whitney out on the deck with my guitar. You sat in the sun the way you always did. Upright on your haunches you enjoyed the view across the valley all the way over to the mountains. I don&amp;#8217;t know if it&amp;#8217;s just boxers but when you sat there stoically and sweetly it just killed me that you were in such dire straits. As I played the song you came over to sit next to me and sniffed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since it was my birthday and the best wife ever was going to a rock show (Foo Fighters) with me, we set you&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>