<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fun on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</title>
    <link>https://socalranch.land/tags/fun/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fun on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2012 15:27:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://socalranch.land/tags/fun/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Egg Hunt</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-04-06-egg-hunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2012 15:27:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-04-06-egg-hunt/</guid>
      <description>An annual Friday afternoon egg hunt &amp;#8230;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunday Painting</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-09-11-sunday-painting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2011 19:23:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-09-11-sunday-painting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hannah and I did some painting this afternoon. We did it out on the front porch because part of the process is making the paints, at least to start. The paint is some all natural stuff that is made from veggies and comes in powder form and gets mixed up with water. From past experience while painting with my daughter &amp;#8211; making up the paint is the least messy part of the session. But I told her that is why we were doing it outside, because it doesn&amp;#8217;t matter if we are messy when we paint outside. We could just hose everything off after &amp;#8211; even her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hannah was a big help scooping the powder out and mixing in the water. OPnce we had the veggie paint set up we each did a few water colors and then she wanted black. Since we couldn&amp;#8217;t make black with the veggie paint Hannah finished up with the pre-mixed tube paints. When can I tell if her affinity with back is a goth tendency? Since I was not about to put paint all ovar myself to do handprints like she was I started trimming lilac shrubs. Then, when she was done I hosed Hannah, the&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>