<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Books on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</title>
    <link>https://socalranch.land/categories/books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Books on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 13:54:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://socalranch.land/categories/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary Of The Doodle Book</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-03-21-summary-of-the-doodle-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 13:54:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-03-21-summary-of-the-doodle-book/</guid>
      <description>I finished the Doodle Revolution book this morning by Sunni Brown. Overall it taught me that questions are about systems, processes or comparisons (sometimes comparing one system or process to another). These questions lead to meetings with communication, understanding (or lack thereof) and ideas. The addition of those three things lead to answers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I See You</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-10-16-i-see-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2013 11:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-10-16-i-see-you/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Earth Abides</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-06-28-earth-abides/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2013 23:49:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-06-28-earth-abides/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;m re-reading Earth Abides by George R Stewart. This stuck out at me: &amp;#8216;The people who live in any generation do much, he realized, either to create or to solve the problems for the people who come in the generations later.&amp;#8217;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not Quite Fake</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-06-01-not-quite-fake/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 08:51:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-06-01-not-quite-fake/</guid>
      <description>[](http://hippeelee.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2011/06/hop.jpg)Hannah&#39;s first book that she actively tried to read herself. &amp;nbsp;
Hannah is not quite reading the Dr. Seuss book, &amp;#8220;Hop On Pop.&amp;#8221; Despite the drama that seems to have become part of the night night routine, I really like reading books with her. She has me point to the words and read them and then she copies me. She gets impatient when there are more than one sentence and uses the pictures as context and reads ahead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Questions, No Answers</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-05-24-questions-no-answers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 22:55:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-05-24-questions-no-answers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;How can I create an interface if everyone is different &amp;#8211; does things in different ways, prefers their favorite flavors which are different from mine &amp;#8230; has a different emotional reaction than I do?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Previously this seems to have been handled with convention and the law of mass average, The law of mass average is my understanding that if you put a jar full of jellybeans out and ask people to guess the number almost everyone will be wrong. If you average the guesses from everyone you will be very close to the correct answer. This is what convention is. Everyone gets together when they use the same service and interacts with it differently. They buy the same product and react to it on different levels and then give feedback to the provider. It&amp;#8217;s minimal, but even no feedback is feedback for the provider.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#8217;m starting The Dark Tower again. I&amp;#8217;m not sure how many times, but I&amp;#8217;ve read the first four books more then ten times now, a bit less for the last three though. I first line is epic in scale: (&amp;#8220;The man in black fled west and the gunslinger followed&amp;#8221;). -Note I need to verify the accuracy of my memory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Object Matters</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-05-21-object-matters/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2009 19:38:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-05-21-object-matters/</guid>
      <description>From the book JavaScript: The Good Parts is this little gem.
The lineage of an object is irrelevant. What matters about an object is what it can do, not what it is decended from.
&amp;#8230;
Prototypal Inheritance:
You start by making a useful object. You can then make many more objects that are like that one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strange Night</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-07-25-strange-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 08:51:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-07-25-strange-night/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It was a strange feeling to go over the M&amp;amp;S&amp;#8217;s last night with Julie gone and myÃ‚Â parentsÃ‚Â watching Hannah. Hannah did great last night. WeÃ‚Â wentÃ‚Â through her usual routine of playing, eating, and shower. Since it was only 6:30 Papa Rosa and I went to the auto part store to get a new distributer cap andÃ‚Â rotorÃ‚Â thingy. Hannah came with us and took a light nap on the way there. The auto store woke her up though and she stayed awake until we got home. She wasn&amp;#8217;t quite all the way tired so Mom played with her till she put her to bed. She stayed down all night! It was reported to me yesterday that she can stand on her own and take three or four steps at a time all by herself. I&amp;#8217;ll have to get a video of that. I can maybe post it on the website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hannah woke up this morning is a very smiley mood. She drank her bottle in less than ten minutes and then started crawling all over me and looking at the animals. We got up and went downstairs to get breakfast ready and Momma Rosa made Papa Rosa feed Hannah. She&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No tooth but I saw Eels</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-04-10-no-tooth-but-i-saw-eels/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2008 12:55:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-04-10-no-tooth-but-i-saw-eels/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;No tooth for Hannah yet. She was really happy this morning though and is still drooling like a mad baby and I am pretty sure that she does not have rabies. That means she is still getting closer to popping that first tooth. SHe is eating pretty well now, she really likes fruit. Julie told me that she ate the whole serving of bananas this morning.Ã‚Â It seems Hannah likes bananas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I saw the eels show last night. Went with M my neighbor and a group of people. Was a good show at the Fox Theater in Boulder. A little crowded but atmosphere was pretty intimate and he puts on an entertaining show. He played a wide range of selections (old and new) and I found out that he is a really good drummer. Before the show they were playing the DVD that came out with his latest album. I saw that he also has a book so I found it on amazon this morning and placed an order. Should be an interesting read.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It snowed today and I think that will hold up Cheryle and Paul. They stayed in Grand Junction last night and will get here today if there isn&amp;#8217;t&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>