<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AtHome on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</title>
    <link>https://socalranch.land/categories/athome/</link>
    <description>Recent content in AtHome on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2015 04:25:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://socalranch.land/categories/athome/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Where I Came From</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2015-08-08-where-i-came-from/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2015 04:25:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2015-08-08-where-i-came-from/</guid>
      <description>You can never escape your past and sometimes it gives you a happy return. Hannah found an old Ohio flag in my closet. I think it&amp;#8217;s from college but can&amp;#8217;t be sure.&amp;nbsp;
She had all kinds of questions why did I have it. Where was it from and what was it for and could she hand it up somewhere. When she stopped to take a breath I told her that I thought it was a great idea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hammocks 101</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2015-03-29-hammocks-101/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2015 20:11:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2015-03-29-hammocks-101/</guid>
      <description>Here are some tips on how best to enjoy and play with a hammock.
   &amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Red River</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2015-03-01-the-red-river/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2015 19:22:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2015-03-01-the-red-river/</guid>
      <description>While distracted from fixing bugs, I made The Red River. Not the HBO version, the book version. The book is always better than the movie / tv show.&amp;nbsp;
Hannah&amp;#8217;s lined up nicely with mine: ﻿
﻿</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motion Excitement</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-09-05-motion-excitement/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2014 14:54:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-09-05-motion-excitement/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#8217;m following the progress of Zurb&amp;#8217;s Foundation For Apps. They have published some ideas related to erasing the difference between native mobile apps and web apps on a mobile device.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Night Nights From The Past</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-09-01-night-nights-from-the-past/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2014 17:11:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-09-01-night-nights-from-the-past/</guid>
      <description>I was cleaning up some things at home and came across a journal entry I wrote a while ago. I published it chronologically but here is a link for reference: Night Nights</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunday Wind</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-04-28-sunday-wind/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2014 02:03:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-04-28-sunday-wind/</guid>
      <description>I think we need some more wind and perhpas a new kite, this one is missing a piece of the frame.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Draw With Me</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-04-05-draw-with-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2014 15:51:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-04-05-draw-with-me/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a variation on the &amp;#8216;play with me&amp;#8217; or &amp;#8216;what should we do?&amp;#8217; or &amp;#8216;what game can we play?&amp;#8217; questions that I get asked with regularity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary Of The Doodle Book</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-03-21-summary-of-the-doodle-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 13:54:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-03-21-summary-of-the-doodle-book/</guid>
      <description>I finished the Doodle Revolution book this morning by Sunni Brown. Overall it taught me that questions are about systems, processes or comparisons (sometimes comparing one system or process to another). These questions lead to meetings with communication, understanding (or lack thereof) and ideas. The addition of those three things lead to answers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Custom Shelf</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-03-19-my-custom-shelf/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2014 23:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-03-19-my-custom-shelf/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;customization-is-diy&#34;&gt;Customization Is DIY&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wanted a custom shelf and didn&amp;#8217;t think any of the usual suspects would have something like I wanted in the price range I wanted. So I&amp;#8217;m going to make my own. Like cooking, the more I do for myself the closer I get to what I want. Perhaps this is because economies of scale must make compromises and I have to make compromises when I dim (do it myself). It&amp;#8217;s just that I can supply the skill and choose which compromises I care about most.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your First Protoype</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-03-19-your-first-protoype/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2014 16:38:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-03-19-your-first-protoype/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;get-past-the-first-one&#34;&gt;Get Past The First One&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Get past the first Protoype as fast as you can. It&amp;#8217;s not going to be perfect but, it should solve your problem and give you a handle on the problem space. This is just the painful birthing process where your idea leaves the mind and enters the world.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chalk Time</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-03-14-chalk-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2014 01:37:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-03-14-chalk-time/</guid>
      <description>I like doing art with Hannah. She thinks I know what I&amp;#8217;m doing. All I do is fallback on the things I know and make the rest up as I go along.
Chalk is my favorite medium to play outside together with her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Thing I Have</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-03-04-one-thing-i-have/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2014 05:33:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-03-04-one-thing-i-have/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There are other things. But tonight the camera in my pocket is worth priceless. When I was a kid and I helped do repair it was taking things apart to see what could be salvaged and putting them back together if there was a way or we could get the right parts to replace.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cork Board Layout</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-02-07-cork-board-layout/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 12:51:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-02-07-cork-board-layout/</guid>
      <description>I was laying a mixture of landscape and portrait photos. My constraints were:
&amp;#8211; grid like structure
&amp;#8211; on a cork board medium
&amp;#8211; one center of focus
&amp;#8211; even (ish) distribution
&amp;#8211; minimum effort today
Physically doing the layout made me wish I had css3 or iOS auto layout to assist and tweak. It only took four tries ( including previous prototypes ) with some help from my two trusty assistants to get it the way I wanted it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quadruple A Weekend Hack (aaaa)</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-01-25-quaddruple-a-weekend-hack-aaaa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 22:25:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-01-25-quaddruple-a-weekend-hack-aaaa/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One of my new Xmas toys was a stylus that has pressure sensitivity and other things available if the app developer implements it. It talks Bluetooth and unfortunately wacom decided to use aaaa batteries to power it. No store in the area carry them and all the shady sellers on amazon ( shady because they send them without being in original packaging even though they picture them as such. About half of the reviewers received dead or expired batteries ).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bundle Bit Removal</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-11-24-bundle-bit-removal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 17:25:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-11-24-bundle-bit-removal/</guid>
      <description>Used when I copied my laptop photo library into a media archive and Finder saw the parent directory as a package instead of a folder.
 xattr -d com.apple.FinderInfo ~/Desktop  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I See You</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-10-16-i-see-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2013 11:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-10-16-i-see-you/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Me</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-09-15-new-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2013 03:10:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-09-15-new-me/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;ve been using Procreate more and more. It is steadily replacing Paper by 53 as my go to app to sketch, mock or doodle. I don&amp;#8217;t know if it&amp;#8217;s the weird tone the support staff takes in papers forums (and the sad we&amp;#8217;re just like Apple and we know what&amp;#8217;s best for you attitude; without even knowing why Apple can get away with it and they can&amp;#8217;t) or the Pro part of Procreate: a free downloadable book for the manual, layers and I can import things into the app to draw on top of.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Glittery Sunday</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-09-09-the-glittery-sunday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2013 03:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-09-09-the-glittery-sunday/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This morning Hannah and I did some glitter art. It was inspired by her &amp;#8216;discovery&amp;#8217; of some packets of glitter I found while cleaning the garage last weekend. She &amp;#8216;found&amp;#8217; them on my workbench in the garage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We each took charge of one paper but helped each other decorate and gave advice on the art direction for the others project. I&amp;#8217;ll leave it up to you to guess who&amp;#8217;s is who&amp;#8217;s.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KeeKee Gets Frisky</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-09-06-keekee-gets-frisky/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2013 03:56:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-09-06-keekee-gets-frisky/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/20130905-205721.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/20130905-205721.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;20130905-205721.jpg&#34; class=&#34;alignnone size-full&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;KeeKee is our cat. Sometimes he gets frisky and starts playing rough.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Those Old Shoes</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-08-21-those-old-shoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2013 03:07:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-08-21-those-old-shoes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I sent this into &lt;a href=&#34;https://uncommon.cc&#34;&gt;uncommon&lt;/a&gt;. They ask nice questions. Here is my answer to this one: **Is there something you&amp;#8217;ve lost that you&amp;#8217;ve never forgotten?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was three, maybe four years old in northeastern Ohio on an autumn afternoon. My parents made us rake up the leaves one afternoon. It was one of those magical afternoons. Where the sunlight filters down through the mature forest and motes of dust hang between oaks, silver maples and beech trees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I took my shoes off, like I still do. There is nothing like the feeling of green grass and crunchy leaves underfoot.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pop! I Hear A Fairy</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-08-03-pop-i-hear-a-fairy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2013 10:14:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-08-03-pop-i-hear-a-fairy/</guid>
      <description>The tooth fairy that is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>805 Links</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-07-01-805-links/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2013 08:03:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-07-01-805-links/</guid>
      <description>A list of links from the 805 (From the father&amp;#8217;s day edition) magazine that I want to remember and checkout:
 ironandresin.com dronefly.com thehandlebarbarshop.com  A list or restaurants to remember:
 publicschool805.com &amp;#8211; went here Aug 02, 2013 for pseudo anniverary dinner. Fish and chips was good. oliopizzaria.com pedalersfork.com  Other things I liked:
 Vespa moto guzzi v7 racer ( but not as much as the BMW street bike) book: the last American man by Elizabeth Gilbert kasbah 3845D rug  Toasting tips:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Explaining Squares With Paper</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-06-16-explaining-squares-with-paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2013 12:13:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-06-16-explaining-squares-with-paper/</guid>
      <description>I was doing math with Hannah this morning and we made a graph of squares using the Paper App.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summertime Milestone</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-06-14-summertime-milestone/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 07:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-06-14-summertime-milestone/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;#8217;t believe she is moving on from kindergarten. It seems like the long days of home work and coordinating drop offs, pickups and school events coalesce into a brief moment that passes by while I was blinking.
Now she can read, to me. Now she can do math, well adding and subtracting. Now she has bff&amp;#8217;s &amp;#8211; although they are quite dynamic. Now she can dress herself for uniform days or free dress days and she knows better than info what the rules are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leprechaun Trap</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-03-15-leprechaun-trap/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 09:42:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-03-15-leprechaun-trap/</guid>
      <description>I worked on a project with Hannah this week. We had to design and implement a Leprechaun trap that she could assemble at school. We were constrained to using materials found at home and that could be assembled at school.
We had two designs. The first, using an empty tissue box, was inspired by the raccoon traps in the book &amp;#8216;Where the Red Fern Grows.&amp;#8217; The trapping idea was that we would put something shiny in it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temporally Configurable Light Programs</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-02-17-temporally-configurable-light-programs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 10:47:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-02-17-temporally-configurable-light-programs/</guid>
      <description>I want lights that are quickly configurable. There are two lights in Hannah&amp;#8217;s room and I turn them off several times a day. I want a program to manage it for me that can:
 handle all the lights in the room, hard wired or plugged into an outlet manage independent schedules for each light understand motion knowledge in the room for smart management work with a simple UI from any device, like Nest</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunday Activity</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-02-10-sunday-activity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 18:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-02-10-sunday-activity/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Part</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-01-08-the-best-part/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2013 00:19:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-01-08-the-best-part/</guid>
      <description>The best part about being a papa is that I get to watch her snuggle after I re-cover her up on a cold night and I see her snuggle into the warmth. Today is good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Year, New Look</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-12-24-new-year-new-look/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2012 10:42:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-12-24-new-year-new-look/</guid>
      <description>Lets get ready for the new year and start with this blog. We start by cleaning out all the old cobwebs in the corners and strip the structure down to its framework. Just the bare skeleton for now. Thats easy and I can do it in a few minutes with AM coffee. WHile I still like the old theme, it was purchased from ThemeForest over two years ago and it is showing its age in web years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back To Sorting</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-09-20-back-to-sorting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2012 22:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-09-20-back-to-sorting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Not the algorithmic kind, the real kind. The kind of sorting that was around long before even the &lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Antikythera_mechanism&#34;&gt;first computer&lt;/a&gt;. Back then, perhaps I had some coins. Coins used to be a popular way to facilitate exchanges. So there we were back when this ancient computer was built. But we didn&amp;#8217;t care about  the computer. I had coins, you had beans, lets talk and make an exchange. Being competitive, I wanted as many of your beans for as few of my coins as possible. And thats where sorting comes in.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Moving On</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-08-01-on-moving-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2012 00:25:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-08-01-on-moving-on/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A reflection that is two months wide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tips for working with a moving company.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2012 Balloon Launch @ Vista Ridge</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-05-20-2012-balloon-launch-vista-ridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2012 20:47:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-05-20-2012-balloon-launch-vista-ridge/</guid>
      <description>Ah, morning coffee and a nice walk over to the clubhouse. Much better today than yesterday; I was warmer and I felt better. I have about a hundred pictures posted to Google+ that I shared with Family and Friends. Let me know if you can&amp;#8217;t find them.
These are my favorite pictures of the morning.
          </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>High Ringbone</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-05-09-high-ringbone/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2012 18:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-05-09-high-ringbone/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;No, it&amp;#8217;s not a new drug. As we get Bobo ready to travel, we had a few things checked out. You know the things that you have happened and seemed little or odd but have corrected themselves with some rest a time? We have noticed Bobo being sore since Decemberish. I think that was that last time I remember Julie riding him. He has always been sore after being trimmed and there have been a few times when he was to sore to ride. So when the vet that did his Coggins test and other things said he was worried about foundering Julie took notice. Me, I don&amp;#8217;t know much about what that means as I married into horses and am learning as I go. Here are my notes about High Ringbone and what is means for Mr. Bobo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This morning the farrier, who gave me an excellent crash course into the physics of horse hoof anatomy, told me that he suspected Bobo had arthritis and it was causing High ringbone &amp;#8211; in my layman and unscientific terms is ossification around the top of his pastern bones that causes spurs to form in the front and on the sides where the joint&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Creativity Starts</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-03-12-where-creativity-starts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2012 11:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-03-12-where-creativity-starts/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was trying to sleep in the other day. Usually, up and at &amp;#8217;em by 6:30 I was stalling. I think it was related to the time change. I have never been a fan of it and it throws everything off for a few days. Even Hannah was up later than usual. I wanted to lay still for a while longer and read some more of the &lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Foundation_series&#34;&gt;Foundation&lt;/a&gt;. It&amp;#8217;s funny how unconnected things can link together in related ways. Yesterday&amp;#8217;s trip to the Butterfly Pavilion and the free kit in cellophane that Hannah got, kinderart projects and learning about animals and bugs combined witha bit of parental laziness and desire for just a few more minutes of morning quiet time lying still unexpectedly gave me a great present.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to lie still for a few more moments, we had to convince Hannah to be a bit more autonomous. The easiest way to do this is with the iPad because it is bigger than her touch and the games are more fun on it. &amp;#8220;Hannah, do you want to take the iPad and Whitney into your room for a little while longer?&amp;#8221; When she is not asking me to make pancakes, she&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fix Everything With Tape</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-12-21-fix-everything-with-tape/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2011 21:13:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-12-21-fix-everything-with-tape/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;padding: 10px; clear: both;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;a class=&#34;alignleft size-medium wp-image-2929&#34; title=&#34;TapeFix-3&#34; href=&#34;http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2011/12/TapeFix-2.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;aligncenter size-medium wp-image-2928&#34; title=&#34;TapeFix-2&#34; src=&#34;http://192.241.192.98/wp-content/uploads/2011/12/TapeFix-2-300x199.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; width=&#34;225&#34; srcset=&#34;http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2011/12/TapeFix-2-300x199.jpg 300w, http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2011/12/TapeFix-2-768x510.jpg 768w, http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2011/12/TapeFix-2-1024x680.jpg 1024w, http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2011/12/TapeFix-2.jpg 1280w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;alignright size-medium wp-image-2929&#34; title=&#34;TapeFix-3&#34; href=&#34;http://192.241.192.98/wp-content/uploads/2011/12/TapeFix-3-300x199.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;aligncenter size-medium wp-image-2928&#34; title=&#34;TapeFix-3&#34; src=&#34;http://192.241.192.98/wp-content/uploads/2011/12/TapeFix-3-300x199.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; width=&#34;225&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fix the kiddo bench with tape.&lt;/strong&gt; There was an issue with the Ikea bench after four years of heavy use. Hannah informed us that it broke but she didn&amp;#8217;t break it. As a proactive measure though, she fixed it with tape. How creative I think to myself when we had this conversation. And, how awesome to get to witness that comprehension, observe her growth in understanding. Maybe it is just me but the observational apsect of being a parent is fascinating. As for Hannah, she knows tape is sticky and that one can tape things together. The bench needs something sticky to keep it securely on. That makes sense. If I knew what she knows I think I would do the same. Of all the things I ever thought were cool, this is up there as the coolest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2011/12/TapeFix-1.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;aligncenter size-medium wp-image-2927&#34; title=&#34;TapeFix-1&#34; src=&#34;http://192.241.192.98/wp-content/uploads/2011/12/TapeFix-1-300x199.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;199&#34; srcset=&#34;http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2011/12/TapeFix-1-300x199.jpg 300w, http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2011/12/TapeFix-1-768x510.jpg 768w, http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2011/12/TapeFix-1-1024x680.jpg 1024w, http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2011/12/TapeFix-1.jpg 1280w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Decorate the fish tank.&lt;/strong&gt; There was a morning tummy ache yesterday. Julie stayed home with H but still had to do some work stuff. I guess she was on a conference call when Hannah decorated the fish tank. There is tha card we got from John and Lori after Grugi died and some kinderart to start with. I think the fishy&amp;#8217;s will enjoy the&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Land Of Pleasant Surprises</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-11-10-the-land-of-pleasant-surprises/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 06:55:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-11-10-the-land-of-pleasant-surprises/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Julie had a long day yesterday. She is in her yearly crunch time with the end of the year stuff they do and yesterday she also had an appointment to disguise her true hair color from me 😉&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So Hannah got me up at 5:15ish in the morning and we saw her off and then played games. I took her to school and then finished up my testing on how to automatically convert a range of productivity documents into images or pdfs based on the file extension. It works and I hope it helps ease the users pain so that they can work with the tools their company provides for them in a way that interacts more seamlessly with our tool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps thats what life should be about. Finding someones pain and creating a way to help deal with it. No one can take pain away. I can ease some of it away through acknowledgment; ven implied acknowledgement with a new workflow in the application, can go a long way to easing someones pain. And then they can redirect their efforts towards things that are important to them which will hopefully ease their pain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then I picked Hannah up from school and boy did&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gurgi&amp;#8217;s Last Day</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-10-16-gurgis-last-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2011 12:45:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-10-16-gurgis-last-day/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It was a cool crisp fall day. The storms of the day before had moved of to the east. We got up early with the sunrise and had a simple breakfast. Toast for me and scrambled eggs, turkey bacon and grilled chicken for you. Sitting around is never good for the soul so we went out to Mr BoBo. Hannah rode in the arena and you and Whitney chased him for a bit, like you always do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We came back home and I took care of a few things around the house. Once I got done I joined you and Whitney out on the deck with my guitar. You sat in the sun the way you always did. Upright on your haunches you enjoyed the view across the valley all the way over to the mountains. I don&amp;#8217;t know if it&amp;#8217;s just boxers but when you sat there stoically and sweetly it just killed me that you were in such dire straits. As I played the song you came over to sit next to me and sniffed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since it was my birthday and the best wife ever was going to a rock show (Foo Fighters) with me, we set you&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Fishys</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-09-15-new-fishys/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2011 07:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-09-15-new-fishys/</guid>
      <description>Hannah helped me pick out some new fish last night. Mr. Fishy died a few weeks ago when the tank had an oxygenation issue.
Since it was book club night Hannah and I had Mac n&amp;#8217; Cheese and then went to the pet store. She looked at all the fish but was more interested in the cats. She didn&amp;#8217;t want to choose I guided her into the Black Mollies and the Neon Tetras.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunday Painting</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-09-11-sunday-painting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2011 19:23:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-09-11-sunday-painting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hannah and I did some painting this afternoon. We did it out on the front porch because part of the process is making the paints, at least to start. The paint is some all natural stuff that is made from veggies and comes in powder form and gets mixed up with water. From past experience while painting with my daughter &amp;#8211; making up the paint is the least messy part of the session. But I told her that is why we were doing it outside, because it doesn&amp;#8217;t matter if we are messy when we paint outside. We could just hose everything off after &amp;#8211; even her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hannah was a big help scooping the powder out and mixing in the water. OPnce we had the veggie paint set up we each did a few water colors and then she wanted black. Since we couldn&amp;#8217;t make black with the veggie paint Hannah finished up with the pre-mixed tube paints. When can I tell if her affinity with back is a goth tendency? Since I was not about to put paint all ovar myself to do handprints like she was I started trimming lilac shrubs. Then, when she was done I hosed Hannah, the&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall Planting</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-08-08-fall-planting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2011 09:20:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-08-08-fall-planting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We got back from Copper Mtn yesterdayaround 2:30 and still had time to got to The Tree Farm and get plants for landscaping the new bed in front of the deck. After some discussion and digging in the ~100 degree sunshine (after riding 80 miles the day before!!!) Julie put in three rows of plants while Hannah (finally) napped:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Grasses in back, next to the railing &amp;#8211; should grow to ~3-4 feet tall, 2-3 feet wide&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Barberry plants &amp;#8211; should grow 2-3 feet tall and 3-4 feet wide&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pretty white flowers (I forget the name) &amp;#8211; should grow to ~1-1.5 feet wide.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did the sprinklers. The rose bed next to he house has 4 drip lines and I think that will work nicely there but it isn&amp;#8217;t planted yet. The garden has three adjustable 360 degree arc sprays with a 5 foot diameter. The nice thing about them is that with the &lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;4&lt;/sub&gt; inch line they can be moved to suit my watering needs. The bed next to the steps has two, 180 degree arcs with an eight foot radius; but, I think I am going to swap them for five foot diameter that have a 360 spray arc with longer &lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;4&lt;/sub&gt; inch connector&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Made This</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-07-31-i-made-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2011 13:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-07-31-i-made-this/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I built this. It is a split level addition to the deck. Complete with rose garden and paved path next to the house that leads to a sitting area (or golfers private driving range?) where you can watch your garden grow as golfers play through just like on tv.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After I got done yesterday (The hottest day of the year) I sat, watched and I enjoyed a cool, refreshing beverage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, after I finished the heavy manual parts, we took Hannah to see a U2 cover band headline one of the Erie Concerts in the park series. I really enjoy them and like it better in the new park. Hannah was fascinated with the band, Once the Chik Fil A cow got out of the way she got her rock and roll dance on. It was fun &amp;#8211; I swung her around, showed her the hop and she carried the Irish flag around for a while. Although I think they do stuff with flag like shapes outside at school and her and Shaye seemed to want to shake the flag more than carry it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Did I mention that this was the hottest day of the year? The car registered 101 when we got the&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hannah and her Volvo</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-07-16-hannah-and-her-volvo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2011 10:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-07-16-hannah-and-her-volvo/</guid>
      <description>This morning while I was doing yard work Hannah did some work of her own. She went to the store (for real this time) and packed for camping. Now we are off to the store for some more sprinkler system parts and wood for the garden boxes.
Watching her at play is educational for me. I think my challenge as a parent is to disguise my advice (tips, tricks and my accumulated knowledge) in a way that she will accept it as her own idea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer Lightning</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-07-13-summer-lightning/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2011 22:07:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-07-13-summer-lightning/</guid>
      <description>%%wppa%%
%%slide=5%%</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Solo Week</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-07-01-the-solo-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2011 21:12:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-07-01-the-solo-week/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;tt&gt;%%wppa%%&lt;/tt&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;tt&gt;%%slide=4%%&lt;/tt&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I read about someone who decides the day before what The Most Important Thing is for the next day. Then, as part of their routine they spend an uninterrupted 90 minutes working on that Thing. Sounds like a good idea. I am a create of habit and routine &amp;#8211; I like the balance it provides.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie and Hannah are heading up to McMinnville next week during Amgen&amp;#8217;s summer shutdown for a week off. I&amp;#8217;m not sure but I think I might be the one getting a week off 🙂 Shhhhhh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So to pseudo plan my solo week routine I have a list of the most Important Things that will need my attention:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Daily walks or rides around with the dogs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ride -&amp;gt; WP&amp;#8217;s bike park is open and the new Valmont bike park needs to be scouted out for fun and to plan future trips with Hannah and perhaps Julie.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Climb. It&amp;#8217;s much more fun than lifting weights.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build The Wall. I think the arc needs to go around to the fence post and then I can step down 3.5 or 4 steps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;del&gt;Stain Pergola. Didn&amp;#8217;t get to last fall or spring &amp;#8230; &lt;/del&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bug AMEX about the claim.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two of the Important Things are really just routines that&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kung Fu Cards (2)</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-06-18-kung-fu-cards-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2011 14:51:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-06-18-kung-fu-cards-2/</guid>
      <description>Hannah made cards with stickers and then gave them away. Her intendeded targets were Shaye, Aunt Katie and Uncle Rob (I think because they were going too the Kung Fu Panda 2 movie with us tonight.Hannah made cards for Shaye, Aunt Katie and Uncle Rob. Here is mine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Early Photoshop</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-04-25-early-photoshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2011 15:29:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-04-25-early-photoshop/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#8217;m running out of things to distract Hannah with. She seems to be feeling better but it&amp;#8217;s only been 3.5 hours since she last spiked a temp of ~103. In an effort to create something for her to do and give myself some more time to play with css for today I resorted to the computer. I have heard enought dora and diego the past three days so I need to be creative in how I present things to her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://hippeelee.com/blog/2011/04/early-photoshop/images/&#34; rel=&#34;attachment wp-att-1905&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;aligncenter size-full wp-image-1905&#34; title=&#34;PBS Logo&#34; src=&#34;http://hippeelee.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2011/04/images1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; width=&#34;226&#34; height=&#34;223&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;so-far-today-8230&#34;&gt;So far today &amp;#8230;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She watched the entire pbs kids am lineup, did playdoh and stamps coloring by herself. She got all the basket toys out and got into an argument with Kee the cat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an effort to get a few more minutes and avoid anything Dora or Diego, I showed her how to use the track pad and made her click through all my links. More css rules are needed. I also want to take some more of the rules out of JavaScript and put it into the stylesheet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When that failed to keep her interested (&amp;#8220;Papa I want to play games on your computer,&amp;#8221; she says to me 🙂 )Enter the old office computer and photoshop. Hannah can use the &amp;#8216;computer pen&amp;#8217;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AM Girl</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-04-19-am-girl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2011 09:24:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-04-19-am-girl/</guid>
      <description>After running a fever for a few days Hannah was back to her usual morning self.Showing off her pigtails and hula hoop</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coordinated Hopping</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-02-24-coordinated-hopping/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 17:46:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-02-24-coordinated-hopping/</guid>
      <description>Hannah was hopping down the stairs this morning every other step.
She was very coordinated until she tried to jump from the bend in the stairs to the floor 🙂</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kiddo Germs</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-02-11-kiddo-germs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 23:50:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-02-11-kiddo-germs/</guid>
      <description>Hannah is running a fever again. On the one hand I know her immune system is getting stronger and more prepared to fight the future. On the other hand I was looking forward to taking her skiing tomorrow While everyone else snowboards.
I hope a good night of child sleep is just the thing she needs to bounce back.
Here are some pictures of me her last weekend. We found a hill close to home and went sledding, made snow sculpture and snow angels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cleaning Girl</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-03-11-cleaning-girl/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 16:25:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-03-11-cleaning-girl/</guid>
      <description>hannah waa a little carpet cleaner today. she helped wash the carpets and looked cool doing it.
she calls the pool, &amp;#8216;the cool&amp;#8217; and i think she wants to go swimming. she tells me she is going to kick her legs and arms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Girl Bed</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-10-21-big-girl-bed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2009 16:34:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-10-21-big-girl-bed/</guid>
      <description>Todo: put the big girl bed together for Hannah.
It seems we can only use the conversion kit or the safety rail. They are not compatible together. I wonder how many times she will fall out before we take the conversion kit off amd use the safety rail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Waiting</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-10-03-waiting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2009 22:10:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-10-03-waiting/</guid>
      <description>Task list
Follow up on truck
3400 python programs (3)
Millers Farm pictures
Prepare for interview
Impromptu example files.
Blog flip script
Redirect or inject a notice to the dom</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Castle Queen</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-09-03-castle-queen/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2009 17:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-09-03-castle-queen/</guid>
      <description>Hannah like to play in her castle with Papa Rosa. She forced him to go in the and sit down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chair Fixing</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-07-18-chair-fixing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2009 15:04:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-07-18-chair-fixing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After we got back from the outlets, Hannah helped me fix her leopard skin chair. Enjoy the movie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then we were putting Bella&amp;#8217;s cat house in the garage. I told Hannah that bella was still missing, it was the first time she really asked much about her since she didn&amp;#8217;t come home for dinner. Then Hannah said, &amp;#8220;Bella work?&amp;#8221; Going to work=missing cat? hmmmm, but I can get that.&lt;figure id=&#34;attachment_1217&#34; style=&#34;width: 300px&#34; class=&#34;wp-caption aligncenter&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://hippeelee.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2009/07/dsc_0427.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;size-medium wp-image-1217&#34; title=&#34;Bella Hunting&#34; alt=&#34;Bella Hunting&#34; src=&#34;http://hippeelee.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2009/07/dsc_0427-300x199.jpg&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;199&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;Bella Hunting&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She says &amp;#8216;Moma work&amp;#8217; when you are already gone for work during the week. And she followed &amp;#8216;Bella work&amp;#8217; with &amp;#8216;Momma work.&amp;#8217; so I asked her if she missed you. she heartily said &amp;#8216;YES!&amp;#8217;. I have also been telling her you are on a ship. She likes ships.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After tidying up a bit and some more fun with crayons I got an Elmo request. I gave her &amp;#8216;Elmo in Grouchland&amp;#8217; and noticed something. She knows when to laugh sometimes and participated a bit when the movie started. Oh yes, i forgot to tell you, she fell asleep last night to Star Wars episode I. She only lasted about 30 minutes or so but she had lots of &amp;#8216;Whats dis?&amp;#8217; and &amp;#8216;Whats dat?&amp;#8217;&lt;figure id=&#34;attachment_1215&#34; style=&#34;width: 300px&#34; class=&#34;wp-caption aligncenter&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://hippeelee.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2009/07/dsc_29261.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;size-medium wp-image-1215&#34; title=&#34;Hand. Hand&#34; alt=&#34;dsc_29261&#34; src=&#34;http://hippeelee.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2009/07/dsc_29261-300x199.jpg&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;199&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;Hand. Hand&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt; &lt;figure id=&#34;attachment_1214&#34; style=&#34;width: 300px&#34; class=&#34;wp-caption aligncenter&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://hippeelee.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2009/07/dsc_29211.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;size-medium wp-image-1214&#34; title=&#34;Babble Babble&#34; alt=&#34;Babble Babble&#34; src=&#34;http://hippeelee.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2009/07/dsc_29211-300x199.jpg&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;199&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yardwork Done</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-07-02-yardwork-done/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2009 17:05:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-07-02-yardwork-done/</guid>
      <description>Things accomplished this spring:
Planted 4 trees
Made three flower beds
Replanted grass
Resurfaced patio
Cleaned garage
Thats all i can think of right now. Tired.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Am Amazed</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-03-27-i-am-amazed/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2009 07:39:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-03-27-i-am-amazed/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So the late winter snowstorm threw a monkey wrench into my plans. Cheryle and Paul&amp;#8217;s flight was canceled so I get to swap snowboarding for Hannah duty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So far today we have had our morning coffee and milk, opened and closed the blinds over fifty times and played 52 card pickup with the flash cards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What amazed me though is that Hannah decided it was elmo time and she didn&amp;#8217;t want to read the books. She went over the the tv (which i forgot to re -child lock) and opened the door to the DVD player where her elmo DVD&amp;#8217;s are, picked up Sesame Street &amp;#8211; Count With Me DVD and tried to put it into the player. All this just from watching me and Julie put dvds in to play. Amazing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#8217;ll trade snowboarding for Hannah time anyday because riding is always there, but I can never have enough Hannah time. And she will only be little once.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our plans for later today are to go to REI and exchange my hat, visit Julie in Longmont for lunch, look for a split board at the store Julie said is going out of business, naps and shoveling the driveway so it doesn&amp;#8217;t turn into a&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Weekend</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-03-23-spring-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2009 09:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-03-23-spring-weekend/</guid>
      <description>Well Spring arrived in a big way this weekend with clear blue skys and temps in the mid 70&amp;#8217;s. Yesterday, e got the lawn ready by power raking it and top seeding. Hannah helped us by bonking her head three times and falling off the patio once, right on her face.
What else did we do, On Saturday we went to the REI grand opening at the Orchard Town Center Mall but did not stand in line for the free gift cards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yea Day</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-03-07-yea-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2009 11:52:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-03-07-yea-day/</guid>
      <description>Busy morning. Got tons of stuff done 🙂
Changed the oil in the Murano. I&amp;#8217;ll drop off the used stuff on our way to the butterfly zoo later today but I still need to find a place for used oil filters.
Waxed poetic on my snowboard so I am ready for some speed runs down the cirque. I hope that the cornice drop is still at the top of the run I was riding a few weeks ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly ToDo&amp;#8217;s</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-02-17-weekly-todos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2009 09:35:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-02-17-weekly-todos/</guid>
      <description> Take Volvo in for service on wednesday Clean House  Bathrooms:Master, Hannahs, Downstairs Dust: bedrooms, Office, G5, Dowsnstairs Vacuum: Upstairs, Downstairs Kitchen: Countertops, sweep floor, mop floor  Sell back some Wii games and buy Mario Kart MERE: install wp software and plugins needed, set up the custom theme Pets: Ride BoBo three times, take pups for runs/walks three times Write 2 shell scripts Papa Mac Session with dad Home Depot for garden mods  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Year, New Sign</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-01-03-new-year-new-sign/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2009 13:57:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-01-03-new-year-new-sign/</guid>
      <description>Hannah signed &amp;#8216;horse&amp;#8217; for me the other day. The only thing is she thinks all harses are called &amp;#8216;BoBo&amp;#8217;.
Other stuff: got the lights taken down and the truck running today. It&amp;#8217;s prolly not the fuel pump. Maybe the cold start sensor? I&amp;#8217;ll need to do some more googling to see what the internets say.
Other things to do: finish the script to grep out five images from the blog images.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Project</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-11-25-weekend-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2008 18:25:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-11-25-weekend-project/</guid>
      <description>It was a semi lazy weekend. I did get one project completed though. Here are the fruits of my labor.
We are headed out to Utah tommorow, for turkey day 2008, at about 5am, perhaps earlier if my crazy 🙂 wife has her way. That should put us in Salt Lake City by mid-afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Got the lights finished, Hannah &amp;#8230;</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-11-24-got-the-lights-finished-hanna/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 22:57:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-11-24-got-the-lights-finished-hanna/</guid>
      <description>Got the lights finished, Hannah fed put to bed and some personal work done this evening. All in all, a good end to this day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend ToDo List</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-10-22-weekend-todo-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2008 15:45:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-10-22-weekend-todo-list/</guid>
      <description> Winterize Sprinkler System Fertilize Lawn Change Oil in Murano Take Volvo in for tire rotation Bring plants in from front porch Fall Pictures Horse swap sale &amp;#8211; looking for an easy to put on winter blanket for Bo take Hannah (the lion) to the Trunk or Treat (didn&amp;#8217;t go) price Murano tires at costco dog food @ Costco  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All Green Lights</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-10-08-all-green-lights/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2008 09:01:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-10-08-all-green-lights/</guid>
      <description>It was all green lights this morning on my way to work. I was thinking aboutÃ‚Â Maui next week with the family, and really looking forward to it.
I am off tommorow and here is what I want to get done:
 take Hannah and the pups for jaunt around the long Vista Ridge loop go for a ride on Bo out to the fields by I-25 find the dive book so Hannah can help me review on the plane photoshop a mock up of the graphics I made for my splash page clean the house  I had better get up early so I can get a jump start on that list 🙂</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sideyard 2.0</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-08-31-sideyard-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2008 16:53:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-08-31-sideyard-20/</guid>
      <description>Labor Day is for doing labor, right? Anywho, I re-did the side to make it look less getto and to stop Mr. Gurgi from esacaping. Alas, when we did a test run by taking Hannah to the pool, one last time before summer ends, he escaped and was in the back yard! Julie thinks he jumped on the dog house and then jumped the fence and that&amp;#8217;s why he couldn&amp;#8217;t get back over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Sign and a Kiss for Pappa</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-08-29-first-sign-and-a-kiss-for-pappa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2008 10:38:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-08-29-first-sign-and-a-kiss-for-pappa/</guid>
      <description>Julie told me this morning that Hannah signed &amp;#8216;more&amp;#8217; to Marie yesterday. When Marie feeds her lunch she says &amp;#8220;More&amp;#8221; but usually doesn&amp;#8217;t sign it. Hannah gave her the sign when she said it.
This morning when I was holding Hannah she gave me a big, sloppy open mouthed wet kiss instead of turning away and giggling like she usually does. That made my doy no matter what happens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boxers @ Work</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-08-28-boxers-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2008 11:13:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-08-28-boxers-work/</guid>
      <description>I have the side yard (dog run) apart while I fill in the low areas of backfill around the foundation that has sunk. I am also putting a split rail fence, that T&amp;#8217;s off the fenceÃ‚Â separatingÃ‚Â our yard form the neighbors house, with a gate to seperate side yard from back yard. I&amp;#8217;ll also need to spread some some cover material that is not river rock. River rock is quite possibly the worst landscaping material I have ever seen or worked with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your First Word: &amp;#8220;HI!&amp;#8221;</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-08-26-your-first-word-hi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2008 09:56:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-08-26-your-first-word-hi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last night Julie and I decided that your first real word is &amp;#8220;Hi.&amp;#8221; You say hi to everything and its really funny. We were sitting outside on the patio having dinner and you said hi to both Gurgi and Whitney, Bella and a plane flying by in the sky. This morning on the walk to The Heathers, you said hi to the clouds, a few houses, the guy walking his dog, Bella who was following us and Mason and Marie when we got inside the house.Ã‚Â&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I need to remember to bring the video camera to your room when I put you to sleep so I can have it there when you wake up in the morning. Thats when you are most talkative. You are getting better at walking. I haven&amp;#8217;t seen it yet but Marie says you can take 6 steps on your own without any assistance. I betcha that by the time we get to Maui in October you will be mostly walking on your own.Ã‚Â&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your other recent behavior is to point (and say &amp;#8220;Hi&amp;#8221;). You really like it when I point back at you and touch you ET style. You still like to High-Five but pointing is&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nice Weekend</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-07-28-nice-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2008 08:39:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-07-28-nice-weekend/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://hippeelee.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2008/07/p-640-480-1c92917f-2b72-4146-ac49-fc1cc5aee0a1.jpeg&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;alignnone size-full wp-image-364&#34; src=&#34;http://hippeelee.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2008/07/p-640-480-1c92917f-2b72-4146-ac49-fc1cc5aee0a1.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;photo&#34; width=&#34;225&#34; height=&#34;300&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We had a great weekend, even though we missed Julie. While she was off in Cancun relaxing Hannah spent the weekend with my parents showing them her tricks: waving, standing and taking baby steps. When she wants something she is willing to let go of her support and take a step or two towards the object of her desire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We got the bricks returned and the yard work done and even got Hannah some new sandals for the summertime. Even with my parents here, it is hard to take care of Hannah by myself. THe longer Julie was gone I noticed more little things that she did which are easy to take fro granted. I was glad to pick her up last night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh yes, Dad got the truck running again, apparently when I changed the plugs and wires I crossed cylinders 1 and 8). Dodge has a strange firing order on the &amp;#8217;97 Dakota.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Things to do this week before we leave for San Diego:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix the electrical (Measure the diameter of the pvc pipe)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;reset the middle sprinkler range at the top of the backyard&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;text-decoration: line-through;&#34;&gt;reset the bricks where the ants dug sand up&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;text-decoration: line-through;&#34;&gt;reset the bricks around the edge where it has settled a quarter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Patio Done :: Hannah Almost Crawling</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-06-30-patio-done-hannah-almost-crawling/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2008 08:26:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-06-30-patio-done-hannah-almost-crawling/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Patio is done, whew. Julie helped tremendously and I think it was more work than she realized. She was also able to take care of Hannah alot of the time so kudos to her for multi tasking. Cory helped to and its prolly because of him that we got done yesterday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My estimated totals are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bricks and wall blocks moved &amp;#8211; 10,000 to 12,000 lbs&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wall foundation and road base moved &amp;#8211; 22 tons&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mason sand for paver leveling &amp;#8211; 2.5 tons&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Equipment rentals &amp;#8211; one paver saw for a day, one 225lb 14&amp;#8243; ground pounder rented twice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lessons learned &amp;#8211; estimated wall block and pavers is not an exact science&amp;#8230; we have almost a pallet extra of rectangular pavers (but just the right amount of square pavers) and we have about &lt;sup&gt;3&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;4&lt;/sub&gt; of a pallet of extra wall blocks. Next time I need to hire a day laborer to help move stuff from the front the back and seriously consider renting one of the hand powered front end loaders to help with moving/loading/excavating.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Hannah news she is standing like mad (with assistance) and can almost push herself up into a sitting position on her own. I give it a week ands she will be sitting up&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Patio Madness</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-06-23-patio-madness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2008 08:01:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-06-23-patio-madness/</guid>
      <description>I have had a hard time getting back to making regular posts since Vegas. I have also had a hard time getting in my training rides for the 50 mile MTB race coming up. I want to at least be able to finish it in under 7.5 hours.
Hannah is growing so fast now. All she wants to do is stand up. You can put her between the couch and the ottoman and she bounces back and forth moving all around until she plops down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Bust, a Sick Hannah and Building the Patio</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-06-12-vegas-bust-a-sick-hannah-and-building-the-patio/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2008 08:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-06-12-vegas-bust-a-sick-hannah-and-building-the-patio/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Busted in Vegas. It seems that people play jack 4 offsuit offline as well as online. Hah. Oh well, I guess that even though he was playing like a maniac, I should have thought a little more before calling his all in with only top pair after the flop. I played good other that that, there was just one other really bad call that I made. Until I lost to MR J4o I was up about $200, the pot with the maniac was the biggest pot I have ever been in before ($475) I am letting people draw too much I think and I could use a healthy dose of aggression to my game. Other times I bet the flop with what I thought was the best hand but didn&amp;#8217;t follow up on the turn and let one person get a straight and another person get to a flush draw. Hmm, need to start being more aggressive post flop when I play strong hands and hit part of the flop. That might give me more information if I bet or reraise when I am in position. Other that those types of hands (and the J4o) I played well from position. Had&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saturday Morning Training</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-05-18-saturday-morning-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2008 12:43:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-05-18-saturday-morning-training/</guid>
      <description>Went for a training ride around Anthem and Vista Ridge this morning. Started out on a little loop. But ehen I came around by Bo&amp;#8217;s stable I decided to keep going up to highway 52. Over to county line road and then back through Anthem turned my ride into a big loop. I did a second smaller loop for good measure and made it back home before ten am.Ã‚Â
Ride Stats</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hannahs Spring Weekend</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-04-14-hannahs-sprin-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2008 12:06:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-04-14-hannahs-sprin-weekend/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I think Spring finally broke for good this past weekend. Hannah got to spend lots of time with her maternal grandparents. Paul and Cheryle drove up from Thousand Oaks for a long weekend. They watched Hannah while Julie and I cleaned the garage and patched all the cracks from the mud jacking. While I was turning on the sprinklers, Julie went out to ride Bo. Later that night we got a movie date night out of it while the grandparents put Hannah down to bed. From the &amp;#8216;report&amp;#8217; we got later that night she wasn&amp;#8217;t thrilled about not being put down by a regular (Me or Julie) but she rolled with it and let them calm her down and comfort her to lala land. For our date we went and saw 21, which i thought was ok but nothing special.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Sunday we got up early and Julie and I ran in the Canine Classic. It was fun, there were a ton of dogs everywhere and the weather was really nice. Not to hot, not too cold, just right for running 5 kilometers. After the race we went into Boulder for brunch and then went home for a nice mid afternoon siesta.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>