<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reading on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</title>
    <link>https://socalranch.land/categories/reading/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reading on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2013 21:16:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://socalranch.land/categories/reading/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mad Libs (Pink Style)</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-07-25-mad-libs-pink-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2013 21:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-07-25-mad-libs-pink-style/</guid>
      <description>Hannah and I started on her Pink Mad Libs book:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10,000 Hours</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-11-16-10000-hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2008 23:20:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-11-16-10000-hours/</guid>
      <description>Or 416,666666 days: the amount of time one needs to spend doing an activity to have a chance at becoming an expert at it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Election Guide 2008</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-09-30-election-help/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 09:41:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-09-30-election-help/</guid>
      <description>I found this page to help me take a step back look at the candidates with a little less bias. I don&amp;#8217;t think it changes how I am going to vote though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strange Night</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-07-25-strange-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 08:51:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-07-25-strange-night/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It was a strange feeling to go over the M&amp;amp;S&amp;#8217;s last night with Julie gone and myÃ‚Â parentsÃ‚Â watching Hannah. Hannah did great last night. WeÃ‚Â wentÃ‚Â through her usual routine of playing, eating, and shower. Since it was only 6:30 Papa Rosa and I went to the auto part store to get a new distributer cap andÃ‚Â rotorÃ‚Â thingy. Hannah came with us and took a light nap on the way there. The auto store woke her up though and she stayed awake until we got home. She wasn&amp;#8217;t quite all the way tired so Mom played with her till she put her to bed. She stayed down all night! It was reported to me yesterday that she can stand on her own and take three or four steps at a time all by herself. I&amp;#8217;ll have to get a video of that. I can maybe post it on the website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hannah woke up this morning is a very smiley mood. She drank her bottle in less than ten minutes and then started crawling all over me and looking at the animals. We got up and went downstairs to get breakfast ready and Momma Rosa made Papa Rosa feed Hannah. She&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not a Fan of Bourne Books</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-03-12-not-a-fan-of-bourne-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2008 09:26:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-03-12-not-a-fan-of-bourne-books/</guid>
      <description>I am trying to read the three Bourne books by Robert Ludlum. I just can&amp;#8217;t seem to get into them. I thought the first book was kinda slow or dull or both. I am about halfway through the second one and it is just dragging on and on while I don&amp;#8217;t really care about any of the characters. I haven&amp;#8217;t ever read anything by Ludlum before but for all the books he sold I expected a better story that this.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>