<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Weather on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</title>
    <link>https://socalranch.land/categories/weather/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Weather on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2014 02:03:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://socalranch.land/categories/weather/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunday Wind</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-04-28-sunday-wind/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2014 02:03:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-04-28-sunday-wind/</guid>
      <description>I think we need some more wind and perhpas a new kite, this one is missing a piece of the frame.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Those Old Shoes</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-08-21-those-old-shoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2013 03:07:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-08-21-those-old-shoes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I sent this into &lt;a href=&#34;https://uncommon.cc&#34;&gt;uncommon&lt;/a&gt;. They ask nice questions. Here is my answer to this one: **Is there something you&amp;#8217;ve lost that you&amp;#8217;ve never forgotten?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was three, maybe four years old in northeastern Ohio on an autumn afternoon. My parents made us rake up the leaves one afternoon. It was one of those magical afternoons. Where the sunlight filters down through the mature forest and motes of dust hang between oaks, silver maples and beech trees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I took my shoes off, like I still do. There is nothing like the feeling of green grass and crunchy leaves underfoot.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall Planting</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-08-08-fall-planting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2011 09:20:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-08-08-fall-planting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We got back from Copper Mtn yesterdayaround 2:30 and still had time to got to The Tree Farm and get plants for landscaping the new bed in front of the deck. After some discussion and digging in the ~100 degree sunshine (after riding 80 miles the day before!!!) Julie put in three rows of plants while Hannah (finally) napped:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Grasses in back, next to the railing &amp;#8211; should grow to ~3-4 feet tall, 2-3 feet wide&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Barberry plants &amp;#8211; should grow 2-3 feet tall and 3-4 feet wide&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pretty white flowers (I forget the name) &amp;#8211; should grow to ~1-1.5 feet wide.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did the sprinklers. The rose bed next to he house has 4 drip lines and I think that will work nicely there but it isn&amp;#8217;t planted yet. The garden has three adjustable 360 degree arc sprays with a 5 foot diameter. The nice thing about them is that with the &lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;4&lt;/sub&gt; inch line they can be moved to suit my watering needs. The bed next to the steps has two, 180 degree arcs with an eight foot radius; but, I think I am going to swap them for five foot diameter that have a 360 spray arc with longer &lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;4&lt;/sub&gt; inch connector&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Made This</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-07-31-i-made-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2011 13:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-07-31-i-made-this/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I built this. It is a split level addition to the deck. Complete with rose garden and paved path next to the house that leads to a sitting area (or golfers private driving range?) where you can watch your garden grow as golfers play through just like on tv.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After I got done yesterday (The hottest day of the year) I sat, watched and I enjoyed a cool, refreshing beverage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, after I finished the heavy manual parts, we took Hannah to see a U2 cover band headline one of the Erie Concerts in the park series. I really enjoy them and like it better in the new park. Hannah was fascinated with the band, Once the Chik Fil A cow got out of the way she got her rock and roll dance on. It was fun &amp;#8211; I swung her around, showed her the hop and she carried the Irish flag around for a while. Although I think they do stuff with flag like shapes outside at school and her and Shaye seemed to want to shake the flag more than carry it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Did I mention that this was the hottest day of the year? The car registered 101 when we got the&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer Lightning</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-07-13-summer-lightning/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2011 22:07:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-07-13-summer-lightning/</guid>
      <description>%%wppa%%
%%slide=5%%</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Signs Her Name</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-05-11-signs-her-name/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 08:23:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-05-11-signs-her-name/</guid>
      <description>Hannah was decorating a card for Mama Rosa and we told her to sign it. I told her the letters and she wrote them. It ended up on two lines because the blue and the brown decorations were in the way 🙂Hannah&amp;rsquo;s Signiture
In other news, Colorado&amp;#8217;s weather remains predictably unpredictable. Yesterday we had warm temps in the 80&amp;#8217;s and mostly clear and sunny sky&amp;#8217;s. Today it is raining with temps in the mid thirties, cloudy and I saw snow flakes in the air and on cars this morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World Top</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-02-12-world-top/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2011 00:59:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-02-12-world-top/</guid>
      <description>The world is spinning and we are falling down the slope. Here are some pictures of before I took the plunge.
In the one picture I am getting ready to eat lunch on top of the world. The other is black snow left over after they did avalanche control. It was surprisingly fresh and bouncy after I dropped onto it.
    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Double F</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-05-07-double-f/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2010 05:47:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-05-07-double-f/</guid>
      <description>it is a frosty cold friday today. No snow, yet, but its cold enough. The sky is clear and it will be crisp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Afternoon Sun</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-01-25-afternoon-sun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2010 16:08:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-01-25-afternoon-sun/</guid>
      <description>Today we were at he playground with some late afternoon sun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4*</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-12-08-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2009 11:39:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-12-08-4/</guid>
      <description>Brrrr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Placing Pumpkins</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-10-14-placing-pumpkins/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2009 15:44:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-10-14-placing-pumpkins/</guid>
      <description>She is very particular where we put the pumpkins. Very particular since i got a &amp;#8216;Sit Down!&amp;#8217;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Fall Day</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-09-22-first-fall-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2009 07:02:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-09-22-first-fall-day/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep Sleeper</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-07-10-deep-sleeper/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2009 20:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-07-10-deep-sleeper/</guid>
      <description>Hannah is a great sleeper. Tonight she slept through a lightning, thunder and then hail storm.
The storm was a slow rolling system moving in the north east direction. Humidity was 55-60 % but it was hot, around 75-80 degrees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crazy Spring Weather</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-06-11-crazy-spring-weather/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2009 21:59:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-06-11-crazy-spring-weather/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#8217;s raining here tonight. It has rained alot her this spring and is really green. I don&amp;#8217;t think I have seen it this green since I left Ohio.
I am expecting full phenotypic expression in our flora.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tornado</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-06-09-tornado/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2009 16:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-06-09-tornado/</guid>
      <description>I just saw live tornado#2 as I was picking up Hannah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PJ&amp;#8217;s for Amy</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-04-07-pjs-for-amy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2009 08:11:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-04-07-pjs-for-amy/</guid>
      <description>The Pink Elephant pj&amp;#8217;s are for you Amy, since you liked the footie pajamas. I am not much of a fasionista, but, little girl clothes and shoes are pretty darn cute. So much so that I would even say its fun getting Hannah dressed in the morning. More fun than dressing myself since most days I could care less what I put on. When I dress Hannah, I actually think about stuff like matching and what she would like depending on the weather.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More, More, More!</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-09-02-more-more-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2008 09:59:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-09-02-more-more-more/</guid>
      <description>I was feeding Hannah breakfast this morning and she showed me the sign for more! She really enjoyed herÃ‚Â bananaÃ‚Â and oatmeal cereal with yogurt. Almost every time I asked her, &amp;#8220;More eat?&amp;#8221; she did the more sign. It was really cool to see my little girlÃ‚Â communicatingÃ‚Â with me on her own level and I look forward to many more interesting conversations with her. I am especially interested in her world view as she grows and her experiences take her into the wide, wide world.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>