<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HTML5 on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</title>
    <link>https://socalranch.land/tags/html5/</link>
    <description>Recent content in HTML5 on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 09:10:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://socalranch.land/tags/html5/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Eyes Closed and Sitting</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-02-16-eyes-closed-and-sitting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 09:10:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-02-16-eyes-closed-and-sitting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As I sit here and try to see what it is that I want I see hazy unfocused shapes moving around in a milky white fog. What is it I need to do and how do I want to get that done? There is more than just the gears behind the clock face.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It takes quite a bit of time to put the shortest bit of delight together. Delight that is fleeting only because of the amount of thought and attention to detail that went into it. Take &lt;a href=&#34;http://hippeelee.com/julie/vday&#34;&gt;cards&lt;/a&gt; for example. No matter where they are found there is far more time in preparing them for consumption that the actual consumption which could only be a few seconds. They comunicate ideas and emotions simply (at least my favorite ones do) and they do it with extreme efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Think about the last card you gave. Most likely, you picked it up at a store, signed your name to it and sent it on its way. Perhaps you took the time to write a more personal note. All of the hard stuff was done for you: which card stock to use, how many colors to use in the graphic design on the front in inside,&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>