<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</title>
    <link>https://socalranch.land/tags/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2011 18:00:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://socalranch.land/tags/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Avoid Fandango</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-12-18-avoid-fandango/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2011 18:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-12-18-avoid-fandango/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In my second experience with Fandango I like them even worse. We won&amp;#8217;t focus on the lack of usability on their website but to say that it was less than optimal and more than painful to get the information I was trying to find.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Related to this sub par experience with them is the Google Offers (I&amp;#8217;m not sold on the whole internet coupons as a value proposition for myself either but Julie is a bit more trusting than I am) Fandango tickets we purchased and can&amp;#8217;t use because they are expiring before we can use them at a different theater later this week. We already made plans to meet other folks at a specific theater but unfortunately for us crapdango tells me that &lt;strong&gt;Online Ticketing Not Available for this Theater.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Huh, so let me get this straight, they sell movie tickets but when I want to buy them they can&amp;#8217;t sell them to me. I recall the first time I balked because they tried to force me to register for an account and charge me an extra couple of dollars for tickets. I guess I&amp;#8217;m at a loss to the value they provide. I have never had a hard time getting tickets&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>