<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Horseback on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</title>
    <link>https://socalranch.land/categories/horseback/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Horseback on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2013 08:13:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://socalranch.land/categories/horseback/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Night With Horses</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-02-28-a-night-with-horses/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2013 08:13:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-02-28-a-night-with-horses/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We got invited out with some new friends and were lucky enough to see the Cavalia show down I&amp;#8217;m Burbank last night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Little girls, big eyes and some brilliant horseman and horsewomanship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2013/02/20130228-071526.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;alignnone size-full&#34; alt=&#34;20130228-071526.jpg&#34; src=&#34;http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2013/02/20130228-071526.jpg&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Papa</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-06-19-happy-papa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2011 16:43:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-06-19-happy-papa/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;tt&gt;%%wppa%%&lt;/tt&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;tt&gt;%%slide=3%%&lt;/tt&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite my favorite person being in Puerto Rico swimming with giant sea turtles and diving in warm, clear water &amp;#8211; it has been a great Father&amp;#8217;s Day. I prefer to be called Papa but what I prefer and what She Who Matters prefers are often two different things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was able to sleep in until after 7am. That was not as late as I would have preferred but later than I thought my actual wake up call would be. We ate a simple breakfast and then trailered up the Marin cruising bike. We rode with the dogs up by Sheridan Parkway and then down around the Community Center. We ended up back where we started with two tired and thirsty boxers and headed out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before we went to the stores we stopped by the neighborhood drug dealer. I got a coffee and Hannah go Hello Kitty Fruit Juice from 7-11. Then we made three stops. We got a lazer engraved name tag for KeeKee &amp;#8211; the engraving process was pretty cool I told Hannah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Later she asked me, &amp;#8220;Daddy, what is cool?&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I told her &amp;#8220;Cool is something fun to do or be with, like a friend.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8220;Then my friends are cool.&amp;#8221; She said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, we got&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MLK Day at the Stock Show</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-01-20-mlk-day-at-the-stock-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2010 12:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-01-20-mlk-day-at-the-stock-show/</guid>
      <description>We took Hannah down to the stock show in denver and saw the grand prix horse jumping. despite the long day and getting over a bug, Hannah did good. She went with ne into the petting zoo and saw the sights and then the horse jumping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yea Day</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-03-07-yea-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2009 11:52:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-03-07-yea-day/</guid>
      <description>Busy morning. Got tons of stuff done 🙂
Changed the oil in the Murano. I&amp;#8217;ll drop off the used stuff on our way to the butterfly zoo later today but I still need to find a place for used oil filters.
Waxed poetic on my snowboard so I am ready for some speed runs down the cirque. I hope that the cornice drop is still at the top of the run I was riding a few weeks ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WP 1</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-01-04-wp-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2009 10:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-01-04-wp-1/</guid>
      <description>Well the truck made it to Mary Jane but it&amp;#8217;s cold up here, about -4 at 9:30am. Hopefully she&amp;#8217;ll start for me when she cools back down 🙂
Thoughts I had on the way up:
Blender a spindrop logo. A raindrop clear bit colored with a hint of rainbow on it&amp;#8217;s surface and slightly twisted. Around the drop there is an orange halo spinning.
The truck made it home. Had a good 3 hour session.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>