<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hannah Art on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</title>
    <link>https://socalranch.land/tags/hannah-art/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hannah Art on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 08:42:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://socalranch.land/tags/hannah-art/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dinosaurs and Cowgirl</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-07-26-dinosaurs-and-cowgirl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 08:42:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-07-26-dinosaurs-and-cowgirl/</guid>
      <description>I wonder if it is coincidence that Hannah is learning about dinosaurs and cowboys? The movie is playing in theaters now &amp;#8230;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When a dragon came to town &amp;#8230;</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-07-13-when-a-dragon-came-to-town/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2011 15:09:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-07-13-when-a-dragon-came-to-town/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure id=&#34;attachment_2421&#34; style=&#34;width: 300px&#34; class=&#34;wp-caption aligncenter&#34;&gt;[&lt;img class=&#34;size-medium wp-image-2421&#34; title=&#34;Hannah&#39;s Dragon Story&#34; src=&#34;http://192.241.192.98/wp-content/uploads/2011/07/CIMG0246-300x228.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Hannah&#39;s Dragon Story&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;228&#34; /&gt;](http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2011/07/CIMG0246.jpg)&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;Hannah&#39;s Dragon Story&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt; 

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hannah brought home some art yesterday that reminded me of my 3rd and 5th grade teacher. Her name was Mrs. Sweet. She introduced me to the Fantasy genre of reading &amp;#8211; Eddings, Brooks etc. Later, when I had her again in 5th grade she pushed me towards Asimov. I am eternally grateful for the hours of content reading that has followed through the years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In both 3rd and 5th grade there was a Creative Writing time. I forget if it was daily &amp;#8211; but we did it enough that it stuck in my memory. She would write a phrase on the blackboard, something like:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;span-style-color-333333-when-a-dragon-came-to-town-8230-span&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #333333;&#34;&gt;When a dragon came to town &amp;#8230;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our assignment was to complete that sentence and keep writing. I can&amp;#8217;t remember much of what I wrote or even if I was very good at it &amp;#8211; I had a hard time sitting still in school. I do remember that I enjoyed that time because, in her words, &amp;#8220;There is no wrong answer, just keep writing.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;in-the-spirit-of-that-memory-hannah-says&#34;&gt;In the spirit of that memory Hannah says:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #333333;&#34;&gt;She took my house and the dragon ate some of my food.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moving the story forward, I say:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**&lt;span style=&#34;color: #333333;&#34;&gt;The dragon was full and she lay down&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kung Fu Cards (2)</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-06-18-kung-fu-cards-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2011 14:51:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-06-18-kung-fu-cards-2/</guid>
      <description>Hannah made cards with stickers and then gave them away. Her intendeded targets were Shaye, Aunt Katie and Uncle Rob (I think because they were going too the Kung Fu Panda 2 movie with us tonight.Hannah made cards for Shaye, Aunt Katie and Uncle Rob. Here is mine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Signs Her Name</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-05-11-signs-her-name/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 08:23:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-05-11-signs-her-name/</guid>
      <description>Hannah was decorating a card for Mama Rosa and we told her to sign it. I told her the letters and she wrote them. It ended up on two lines because the blue and the brown decorations were in the way 🙂Hannah&amp;rsquo;s Signiture
In other news, Colorado&amp;#8217;s weather remains predictably unpredictable. Yesterday we had warm temps in the 80&amp;#8217;s and mostly clear and sunny sky&amp;#8217;s. Today it is raining with temps in the mid thirties, cloudy and I saw snow flakes in the air and on cars this morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Early Photoshop</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-04-25-early-photoshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2011 15:29:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-04-25-early-photoshop/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#8217;m running out of things to distract Hannah with. She seems to be feeling better but it&amp;#8217;s only been 3.5 hours since she last spiked a temp of ~103. In an effort to create something for her to do and give myself some more time to play with css for today I resorted to the computer. I have heard enought dora and diego the past three days so I need to be creative in how I present things to her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://hippeelee.com/blog/2011/04/early-photoshop/images/&#34; rel=&#34;attachment wp-att-1905&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;aligncenter size-full wp-image-1905&#34; title=&#34;PBS Logo&#34; src=&#34;http://hippeelee.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2011/04/images1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; width=&#34;226&#34; height=&#34;223&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;so-far-today-8230&#34;&gt;So far today &amp;#8230;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She watched the entire pbs kids am lineup, did playdoh and stamps coloring by herself. She got all the basket toys out and got into an argument with Kee the cat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an effort to get a few more minutes and avoid anything Dora or Diego, I showed her how to use the track pad and made her click through all my links. More css rules are needed. I also want to take some more of the rules out of JavaScript and put it into the stylesheet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When that failed to keep her interested (&amp;#8220;Papa I want to play games on your computer,&amp;#8221; she says to me 🙂 )Enter the old office computer and photoshop. Hannah can use the &amp;#8216;computer pen&amp;#8217;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>