<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pets on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</title>
    <link>https://socalranch.land/categories/pets/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pets on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2013 03:56:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://socalranch.land/categories/pets/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>KeeKee Gets Frisky</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-09-06-keekee-gets-frisky/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2013 03:56:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-09-06-keekee-gets-frisky/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/20130905-205721.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/20130905-205721.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;20130905-205721.jpg&#34; class=&#34;alignnone size-full&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;KeeKee is our cat. Sometimes he gets frisky and starts playing rough.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>High Ringbone</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-05-09-high-ringbone/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2012 18:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-05-09-high-ringbone/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;No, it&amp;#8217;s not a new drug. As we get Bobo ready to travel, we had a few things checked out. You know the things that you have happened and seemed little or odd but have corrected themselves with some rest a time? We have noticed Bobo being sore since Decemberish. I think that was that last time I remember Julie riding him. He has always been sore after being trimmed and there have been a few times when he was to sore to ride. So when the vet that did his Coggins test and other things said he was worried about foundering Julie took notice. Me, I don&amp;#8217;t know much about what that means as I married into horses and am learning as I go. Here are my notes about High Ringbone and what is means for Mr. Bobo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This morning the farrier, who gave me an excellent crash course into the physics of horse hoof anatomy, told me that he suspected Bobo had arthritis and it was causing High ringbone &amp;#8211; in my layman and unscientific terms is ossification around the top of his pastern bones that causes spurs to form in the front and on the sides where the joint&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solo Ride</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-10-02-solo-ride/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2011 08:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-10-02-solo-ride/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Julie and Hannah did some Fall maintenance on our pets. After doing that they went for a ride. Hannah rode by herself and learned to steer BoBo in a circle. Watch &amp;#8230;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Later, a very lucky Mr. Kee Kee narrowly escaped becoming a coyote dinner. The coyote jumped the fence chasing him into the neighbors yard. I chansed the coyote away once and then went and got shoes and a flash light. I was gone less than a minute when Mr. Coyote jumped back over. I threw a river rock at him and shooed him away over the hill that sits between us and hole twelve.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A very pissed Mr Kee Kee went to the vet to get checked out. The conclusion is that he was very lucky and Julie and I have decided to enlist Hannah&amp;#8217;s help in keeping Mr. Kee Kee inside &amp;#8211; permanently. Julie did mention that she saw a few unlucky mice (bones) in the x-ray they took of Mr. Kee Kee when he was getting checked out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wish we got the pictures of our e-rays. From personal experience I wish I had a collection of all mine. Not only would it help me keep track of&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Papa</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-06-19-happy-papa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2011 16:43:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-06-19-happy-papa/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;tt&gt;%%wppa%%&lt;/tt&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;tt&gt;%%slide=3%%&lt;/tt&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite my favorite person being in Puerto Rico swimming with giant sea turtles and diving in warm, clear water &amp;#8211; it has been a great Father&amp;#8217;s Day. I prefer to be called Papa but what I prefer and what She Who Matters prefers are often two different things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was able to sleep in until after 7am. That was not as late as I would have preferred but later than I thought my actual wake up call would be. We ate a simple breakfast and then trailered up the Marin cruising bike. We rode with the dogs up by Sheridan Parkway and then down around the Community Center. We ended up back where we started with two tired and thirsty boxers and headed out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before we went to the stores we stopped by the neighborhood drug dealer. I got a coffee and Hannah go Hello Kitty Fruit Juice from 7-11. Then we made three stops. We got a lazer engraved name tag for KeeKee &amp;#8211; the engraving process was pretty cool I told Hannah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Later she asked me, &amp;#8220;Daddy, what is cool?&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I told her &amp;#8220;Cool is something fun to do or be with, like a friend.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8220;Then my friends are cool.&amp;#8221; She said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, we got&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Ladies and a horse</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-03-21-2-ladies-and-a-horse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2010 15:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-03-21-2-ladies-and-a-horse/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movies &amp;#038; Santa</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-12-20-movies-santa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2009 15:18:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-12-20-movies-santa/</guid>
      <description>Julie took Hannah to her first theater movie: The Princess and the Frog.
Later, she had a really funny comment in the car on the way to ride Bobo. Julie had given her the chapstick to use and H wouldn&amp;#8217;t give it back. We had to stop the car to take it from her. Julie explaind that the chapstick was hers and H couldn&amp;#8217;t keep it. H was very upset so i said,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4*</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-12-08-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2009 11:39:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-12-08-4/</guid>
      <description>Brrrr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Coat</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-10-11-new-coat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2009 13:27:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-10-11-new-coat/</guid>
      <description>October has fallen.
I saw the harvest moon.
It snowed and did not melt today.
We took Hannah out to BoBo in her new snow bunny coat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chair Fixing</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-07-18-chair-fixing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2009 15:04:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-07-18-chair-fixing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After we got back from the outlets, Hannah helped me fix her leopard skin chair. Enjoy the movie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then we were putting Bella&amp;#8217;s cat house in the garage. I told Hannah that bella was still missing, it was the first time she really asked much about her since she didn&amp;#8217;t come home for dinner. Then Hannah said, &amp;#8220;Bella work?&amp;#8221; Going to work=missing cat? hmmmm, but I can get that.&lt;figure id=&#34;attachment_1217&#34; style=&#34;width: 300px&#34; class=&#34;wp-caption aligncenter&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://hippeelee.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2009/07/dsc_0427.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;size-medium wp-image-1217&#34; title=&#34;Bella Hunting&#34; alt=&#34;Bella Hunting&#34; src=&#34;http://hippeelee.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2009/07/dsc_0427-300x199.jpg&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;199&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;Bella Hunting&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She says &amp;#8216;Moma work&amp;#8217; when you are already gone for work during the week. And she followed &amp;#8216;Bella work&amp;#8217; with &amp;#8216;Momma work.&amp;#8217; so I asked her if she missed you. she heartily said &amp;#8216;YES!&amp;#8217;. I have also been telling her you are on a ship. She likes ships.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After tidying up a bit and some more fun with crayons I got an Elmo request. I gave her &amp;#8216;Elmo in Grouchland&amp;#8217; and noticed something. She knows when to laugh sometimes and participated a bit when the movie started. Oh yes, i forgot to tell you, she fell asleep last night to Star Wars episode I. She only lasted about 30 minutes or so but she had lots of &amp;#8216;Whats dis?&amp;#8217; and &amp;#8216;Whats dat?&amp;#8217;&lt;figure id=&#34;attachment_1215&#34; style=&#34;width: 300px&#34; class=&#34;wp-caption aligncenter&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://hippeelee.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2009/07/dsc_29261.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;size-medium wp-image-1215&#34; title=&#34;Hand. Hand&#34; alt=&#34;dsc_29261&#34; src=&#34;http://hippeelee.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2009/07/dsc_29261-300x199.jpg&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;199&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;Hand. Hand&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt; &lt;figure id=&#34;attachment_1214&#34; style=&#34;width: 300px&#34; class=&#34;wp-caption aligncenter&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://hippeelee.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2009/07/dsc_29211.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;size-medium wp-image-1214&#34; title=&#34;Babble Babble&#34; alt=&#34;Babble Babble&#34; src=&#34;http://hippeelee.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2009/07/dsc_29211-300x199.jpg&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;199&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bella Dilemma</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-04-14-the-bella-dilemma/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2009 10:57:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-04-14-the-bella-dilemma/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/img_0006.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;alignright size-medium wp-image-964&#34; title=&#34;Bella Sitting&#34; alt=&#34;Bella Sitting&#34; src=&#34;http://192.241.192.98/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/img_0006-225x300.jpg&#34; width=&#34;225&#34; height=&#34;300&#34; srcset=&#34;http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/img_0006-225x300.jpg 225w, http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/img_0006-768x1024.jpg 768w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 225px) 100vw, 225px&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bella has been missing the last few days. Julie last saw her by Black Rock Elementary on Thursday. We have been letting her out during the day because she gets really crazy when she is confined to the house &lt;sup&gt;24&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;7&lt;/sub&gt;. We though she was gone because we didn&amp;#8217;t have a tag with our numbers on there but I just confirmed that she is at the BVHS (Boulder Valley Humane Society).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My dilemma is if we should keep letting her out or not. I am aware of the risks but I wonder if it is crueler to keep her inside all of the time (and crazy) or let her out where she can take her chances and happily goes about her business. I know I would always opt for taking my chances but I am not a cat. Since she is a cat and she can&amp;#8217;t really tell me what she wants, other that to observe her behavior; her behavior tells me that she likes to go outside. I think we will try to find a happy medium: she can still go outside, but only when we are there in the yard. We will also be getting her a tag for her collar&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>