<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Travel on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</title>
    <link>https://socalranch.land/categories/travel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Travel on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2013 16:14:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://socalranch.land/categories/travel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Doodles (that may end up on a t-shirt)</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-07-04-doodles-that-may-end-up-on-a-t-shirt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2013 16:14:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-07-04-doodles-that-may-end-up-on-a-t-shirt/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/20130704-151420.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;alignnone size-full&#34; alt=&#34;20130704-151420.jpg&#34; src=&#34;http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/20130704-151420.jpg&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cleveland Zoo</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-04-18-cleveland-zoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2012 15:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-04-18-cleveland-zoo/</guid>
      <description>After a morning in the garden and reading with Mama Rosa we went down to the Cleveland Zoo to see what we could see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Family Buca</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-08-19-family-buca/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2011 19:51:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-08-19-family-buca/</guid>
      <description>There was an impromptu Iacobucci get together at the Buca Di Peppe in downtown Columbus tonight. There was:
 Good food (Bread, butter and olive oil, pizza, moist chicken that tasted lemony, spagetti, rigatoni, beer and wine) Good conversation Kids &amp;#8216;n Chaos The promise to meet again tomorrow for Susie&amp;#8217;s wedding and do it all over again   Hannah is really having a good time with her cousins &amp;#8211; I think she has semi-adopted Raven and Taylor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walking Nashau</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-04-14-walking-nashau/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2010 14:33:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-04-14-walking-nashau/</guid>
      <description>After day two of the CMS training in Nashau, NH i taxied over to Greely Park and walked along the river.
i was reminded how much fun it is to pretend to be an explorer when walking in the woods, just like I used to do in the Ravine at my childhood home. I think the light filtering through the trees had something to do with it.
I decided to save the $10 cab fare and walk home through some nice nieghborhoods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Funny Thing</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-06-29-funny-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2009 10:26:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-06-29-funny-thing/</guid>
      <description>We stopped at the outlets on our way home from the lilac circle Breckenridge weekend. Hannah was sound asleep when we got out of the car. I carried her into the first store and she heard the music, opened her eyes and started bobbing her head to the music for a minute. Then she closed her eyes and snuggled back down into my shoulder, fast asleep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shells</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-05-14-shells/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2009 06:25:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-05-14-shells/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 OBX</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-05-10-2-obx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2009 11:10:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-05-10-2-obx/</guid>
      <description>If everyone could sleep this well&amp;#8230;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vacation Is Go</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-05-09-vacation-is-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2009 00:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-05-09-vacation-is-go/</guid>
      <description>Vacation week is underway and Hannah is running a fever. This afternoon, she got all snuggly, and then her temp spiked to 104 for a few minutes. 10 long minutes later it was 102 and ten after that it was 100. Forty five minutes later it was normal, mama was home and Hannah was turning around yellng in that todler half speak that she makes up.
I&amp;#8217;m sure traveling will be interesting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Project</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-11-25-weekend-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2008 18:25:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-11-25-weekend-project/</guid>
      <description>It was a semi lazy weekend. I did get one project completed though. Here are the fruits of my labor.
We are headed out to Utah tommorow, for turkey day 2008, at about 5am, perhaps earlier if my crazy 🙂 wife has her way. That should put us in Salt Lake City by mid-afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mini Cali Vacation</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-11-07-mini-cali-vacation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2008 01:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-11-07-mini-cali-vacation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://hippeelee.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2008/11/p-640-480-cda7ea7e-d398-44f8-a703-f19e2da283cc.jpeg&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;alignnone size-full wp-image-364&#34; src=&#34;http://hippeelee.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2008/11/p-640-480-cda7ea7e-d398-44f8-a703-f19e2da283cc.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; width=&#34;225&#34; height=&#34;300&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I traveled with Julie and Hannah to the Conejo Valley, she had training for work. Hannah and I hung out with Grandma Cheryle Today. I got a very good nap when Hannah took hers this afternoon, almost two hours. More of the same, I want to ride Sycamore but I have a couple of other things that I want to get done on the computer first so I may just go over there and get a quick trail run in. I have been running alot lately even though I profess to dislike it. I think that is because it is quick, out the door type exercise and convenient. I think I am going to take one of the rock climbing classes at the rec center this winter. Its been years since my harness has been used and I forget the knots and other stuff thats important.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The weather here is really great. It was sunny and 85 today. It was overcast on Wednesday back in Erie but has cleared up even though fall weather has asserted itself in the last few days. Temperatures are only getting to the mid 50&amp;#8217;s or low 60&amp;#8217;s during the day and at night its getting below&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Trip</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-08-04-weekend-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2008 08:43:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-08-04-weekend-trip/</guid>
      <description>We went to San Diego this weekend and Hannah had a blast. I think it wore her out a little bit though. She got to meed Scott and Sarah&amp;#8217;s new puppy, Aggie and she got to see her Grandma Cheryle and Grandpa Paul while Julie and I went to a wedding. She had a great time with her grandparents and then On Sunday we took her to the San Diego Cove.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>