<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Memories on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</title>
    <link>https://socalranch.land/tags/memories/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Memories on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2012 09:16:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://socalranch.land/tags/memories/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>An Easy Toolchain</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-02-21-an-easy-toolchain/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2012 09:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-02-21-an-easy-toolchain/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I learned about tools from my dad. He used to fix everything us kiddos broke around the house and the cars and other engine driven things we used. I remember he had a method that included starting from the problem and working backwards through the solution. I spent alot of time bored out of my mind, holding his tools. Sometimes I was sent to get different tools but usually he brought a couple of different general purpose tools and was able to make due with them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its funny, the more I learn about software and software development, even from a web slanted view, it all depends on the tools you use. It depends on the tools that work best with your style. I have been keeping my personal projects and org-mode files under version control at bitbucket with mercurial for a few years now and while not completely immersed in the distributed version control environment, I am drawn to the benefits of it. Namely being able to commit to my repo whenever and whereever I am internt access or no internet access.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I ramp up the search for opportunities in the next phase there are a lot of things I still need&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When a dragon came to town &amp;#8230;</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-07-13-when-a-dragon-came-to-town/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2011 15:09:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-07-13-when-a-dragon-came-to-town/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure id=&#34;attachment_2421&#34; style=&#34;width: 300px&#34; class=&#34;wp-caption aligncenter&#34;&gt;[&lt;img class=&#34;size-medium wp-image-2421&#34; title=&#34;Hannah&#39;s Dragon Story&#34; src=&#34;http://192.241.192.98/wp-content/uploads/2011/07/CIMG0246-300x228.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Hannah&#39;s Dragon Story&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;228&#34; /&gt;](http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2011/07/CIMG0246.jpg)&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;Hannah&#39;s Dragon Story&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt; 

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hannah brought home some art yesterday that reminded me of my 3rd and 5th grade teacher. Her name was Mrs. Sweet. She introduced me to the Fantasy genre of reading &amp;#8211; Eddings, Brooks etc. Later, when I had her again in 5th grade she pushed me towards Asimov. I am eternally grateful for the hours of content reading that has followed through the years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In both 3rd and 5th grade there was a Creative Writing time. I forget if it was daily &amp;#8211; but we did it enough that it stuck in my memory. She would write a phrase on the blackboard, something like:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;span-style-color-333333-when-a-dragon-came-to-town-8230-span&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #333333;&#34;&gt;When a dragon came to town &amp;#8230;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our assignment was to complete that sentence and keep writing. I can&amp;#8217;t remember much of what I wrote or even if I was very good at it &amp;#8211; I had a hard time sitting still in school. I do remember that I enjoyed that time because, in her words, &amp;#8220;There is no wrong answer, just keep writing.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;in-the-spirit-of-that-memory-hannah-says&#34;&gt;In the spirit of that memory Hannah says:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #333333;&#34;&gt;She took my house and the dragon ate some of my food.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moving the story forward, I say:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**&lt;span style=&#34;color: #333333;&#34;&gt;The dragon was full and she lay down&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Papa</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-06-19-happy-papa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2011 16:43:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-06-19-happy-papa/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;tt&gt;%%wppa%%&lt;/tt&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;tt&gt;%%slide=3%%&lt;/tt&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite my favorite person being in Puerto Rico swimming with giant sea turtles and diving in warm, clear water &amp;#8211; it has been a great Father&amp;#8217;s Day. I prefer to be called Papa but what I prefer and what She Who Matters prefers are often two different things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was able to sleep in until after 7am. That was not as late as I would have preferred but later than I thought my actual wake up call would be. We ate a simple breakfast and then trailered up the Marin cruising bike. We rode with the dogs up by Sheridan Parkway and then down around the Community Center. We ended up back where we started with two tired and thirsty boxers and headed out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before we went to the stores we stopped by the neighborhood drug dealer. I got a coffee and Hannah go Hello Kitty Fruit Juice from 7-11. Then we made three stops. We got a lazer engraved name tag for KeeKee &amp;#8211; the engraving process was pretty cool I told Hannah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Later she asked me, &amp;#8220;Daddy, what is cool?&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I told her &amp;#8220;Cool is something fun to do or be with, like a friend.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8220;Then my friends are cool.&amp;#8221; She said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, we got&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>