<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Music on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</title>
    <link>https://socalranch.land/categories/music/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Music on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 06:10:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://socalranch.land/categories/music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Quiet I Will Be</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-06-06-quiet-i-will-be/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 06:10:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-06-06-quiet-i-will-be/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I will learn to&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hear and understand&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That ever thing and&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everything will pass&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Into time, it is all&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just in my mind&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas In May</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-05-14-christmas-in-may/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2014 15:03:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-05-14-christmas-in-may/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;optional-titles-best-wife-ever-or-best-present-ever&#34;&gt;Optional Titles: Best Wife Ever or Best Present Ever&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am lucky that my wife knows me. After almost a decade of working with her on our relationship I should not be that surprised. But there I was Christmas morning with an envelope that had a print out from TicketMaster. The first thing through my head was wtf. The second thing, since I knew about the concert and given that it was in the heart of Los Angeles I knew it would be impossible to get a piar of tickets, was how did she ???&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Favorite Things</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-08-25-10-favorite-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 06:39:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-08-25-10-favorite-things/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#8217;m sure this will change with time. Here is my list of 10 favorite things. (prompted by the &lt;a href=&#34;https://uncommon.cc&#34;&gt;uncommon&lt;/a&gt; website)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sonic Cycles</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-08-25-sonic-cycles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 06:05:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-08-25-sonic-cycles/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In life, everything is tied to a cycle, a rhythm and the beat of someones drum. Things pulse and we are drawn to them in unison. Be it music, be it it code (hardware &amp;amp; software) be it a summer festival in the sun. We are all drawn to the light.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For me, music is the light and  I&amp;#8217;m just a fan of anything good. I grew up in northeastern Ohio with the heavy metal hard rock that was really, really fun in the nineties along the Cuyahoga River. Then, Lake Erie and the flats were a great place to experience music and pure Rock &amp;amp; Roll. And then Lallapalooza &amp;#8217;91 came into town and blew my mind. It expand all of the possibilities to the next level that led me to where I am today.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Funny Thing</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-06-29-funny-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2009 10:26:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-06-29-funny-thing/</guid>
      <description>We stopped at the outlets on our way home from the lilac circle Breckenridge weekend. Hannah was sound asleep when we got out of the car. I carried her into the first store and she heard the music, opened her eyes and started bobbing her head to the music for a minute. Then she closed her eyes and snuggled back down into my shoulder, fast asleep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rocking QOTHSA Today</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-04-30-rocking-qothsa-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2009 08:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-04-30-rocking-qothsa-today/</guid>
      <description>Yum, coffee and hard, crunchy guitar rifs with a nice mellow vocal overlay.
Rhythm and life are a repetitive pattern evolving with time. How am I evolving? What am I evolving into?
 &amp;#8220;Little Sister can&amp;#8217;t you find another way? No more living life behind a shadow.&amp;#8221;
 MMmm Crunchy. Rinse and repeat for a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More SomaFM</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-04-29-more-somafm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2009 15:33:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-04-29-more-somafm/</guid>
      <description>I just found out that SomaFM &amp;#8211; Groove Salad is available for the iPhone and over Edge. IT&amp;#8217;s getting addicting and I amy have to pony up some cash for them if I keep usingÃ‚Â theirÃ‚Â bandwidth.
I also think that Groove Salad *sounds*different at night. I was doing homework after mid-night last night and the night before and there were some really cool remixes of songs I have heard before on there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saturday Ride</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-03-28-saturday-ride/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2009 12:52:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-03-28-saturday-ride/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nice day, good weather. I got two nice drops into Vasquez Cirque. It was a little bumpy but there were still some calf/knee high patches and some decent turns leading into them. I need to think about dropping in less, unless I plan on going down one of the rocky chutes, I noticed that my turns feel more natural when I am reacting to the conditions of THIS turn rather than thinking about the next turn or the last turn or the really big rock that is coming up fast.Ã‚Â VisualizationÃ‚Â is still good at the top, it gives me a game plan but plans don&amp;#8217;t always turn out as you would expect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Got two runs down the baby park, popped some nice mellow airs on the baby five footers and the little rails and boxes are always fun. The biggest surprise was the carving and turns on my way back to winter park parking lot. I leaned into some gorgous s-turns and got really good extension both toe side and heel side. There was a bit of corn on the way down too, spring is fast approaching (the last week of weather aside). The last three weekends should be great for&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C is for Cookie</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-03-04-c-is-for-cookie/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2009 17:28:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-03-04-c-is-for-cookie/</guid>
      <description>While getting dinner ready Hannah was enjoying some Seseme Street and cookie monsters favorite song.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It Suits My Mood</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-02-10-it-suits-my-mood/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2009 17:33:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-02-10-it-suits-my-mood/</guid>
      <description>And todays weather.
Cold Desert by Kings of Leon</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>