<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CostRica on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</title>
    <link>https://socalranch.land/tags/costrica/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CostRica on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 May 2011 07:14:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://socalranch.land/tags/costrica/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Pura Vida</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-05-18-pura-vida/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2011 07:14:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-05-18-pura-vida/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is the first Internet access in almost a week. Pura Vida seems to be local slang for &amp;#8220;it&amp;#8217;s all good&amp;#8221; or &amp;#8220;no worries.&amp;#8221; For sure that can describe the past few days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monteverde was lush &amp;#8211; the biodiversity is amazing. I&amp;#8217;m going to have to re-read EO Wilsons book &amp;#8220;The Diversity of Life&amp;#8221; again because it was about places like this. We spent a day in the national park and our guide was very knowledgable of the flora and fauna. She especially liked birds. Besides the forest I saw signs of mountain biking in the area and would be very excited to come back and ride here&amp;#8230;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a too short stay in our almost private resort we drove down the coast to Manuel Antonio and went diving yesterday. Despite the murky visibility we saw a lot ot wildlife. Today the plan is to hike the national park here and end up at the beach. Hannah has gotten a lot of pool time but only a little beach time so far.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#8217;ve gotten some really good pictures but I can&amp;#8217;t post them yet. I&amp;#8217;m using Julies iPad to post this and besides the annoying typing corrections, it lacks the ability to post&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>