<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Selling on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</title>
    <link>https://socalranch.land/tags/selling/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Selling on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 15:15:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://socalranch.land/tags/selling/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Advice From A Salesman</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-03-22-advice-from-a-salesman/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 15:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-03-22-advice-from-a-salesman/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Its a cold dark world. When you find a warm light, even a small flicker cup your hands around it and enjoy the warmth. Nurture it &amp;#8211; if its a candle and the wax is almost gone transfer it to a new candle so it can continue to add light to the world. Science, numbers, logic makes me feel warm because it is easy to internalize ones answer as right or wrong. The answer to the math question is either correct or incorrect or, the function you write has the correct output that you need or it doesn&amp;#8217;t. It doesn&amp;#8217;t matter how you got to the correct output. For most things in life and business, it only matters that you got to the correct answer for a particular problem. Solving any kind of problem &amp;#8211; even small and trivial ones always makes me feel warm inside and adds flicker to my flame.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently I have found myself in an odd position with a problem I am uneducated for and unprepared to solve. Selling my skill set and experience to a range of businesses with unique problems regarding the internet. I like the web and I want to work with web technology to&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>