<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Backpacking on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</title>
    <link>https://socalranch.land/categories/backpacking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Backpacking on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2015 20:11:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://socalranch.land/categories/backpacking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hammocks 101</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2015-03-29-hammocks-101/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2015 20:11:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2015-03-29-hammocks-101/</guid>
      <description>Here are some tips on how best to enjoy and play with a hammock.
   &amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bear Lake Snowboarding</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-02-02-bear-lake-snowboarding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2009 10:05:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-02-02-bear-lake-snowboarding/</guid>
      <description>Had a great day at the RMNP Bear Lake trail system. The only things missing were Julie and Hannah, but I think they might of been a little cold. This picture is of me hiking up to get some turns. Given my limited back country experience it was the first time in a long time that my heart rate was already going even before I dropped in, and, I only hiked halfway up the slope pictured in this picture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Spring Weekend</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-05-05-good-spring-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2008 07:22:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-05-05-good-spring-weekend/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;No traveling, nothing urgent to do this past weekend and good time spent with Hannah made the weekend alot of fun. It started on Friday night when we got all the children together for some dinner. They were very cute playing together. Then we had some Wii time, Smash Bros &amp;amp; Martio Kart. A couple of beers and then off to bed.Ã‚Â&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We got up pretty early and were ready to go hiking on Saturday morning. Just around Betasso Preserve loop ~3.2 miles. Hannah did good on her second training hike, She fell asleep towards the end. On our way back home we stopped for an early lunch at the farmers market. Then it was off to home for a mid day nap. It was a very good nap. Woke up around 3:00 or so and played with Hannah some more while Julie went out to see Mr Bo. We had dinner and put Hannah to bed at her usual time and then watched a movie, Juno. It was pretty good. It gave me an idea for how to manage my Netflix queue. Instead of waiting for them to recommend a move for me, I just look at what is currently&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peep Peep (a little bird awakens, and she wants)</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-04-22-peep-peep-a-little-bird-awakens-and-she-wants-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 09:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-04-22-peep-peep-a-little-bird-awakens-and-she-wants-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peep Peep ( a little birdie awakens )</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-04-22-peep-peep-a-little-birdie-awakens/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 07:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-04-22-peep-peep-a-little-birdie-awakens/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    On Friday, when I fed Hannah dinner, she started a new behavior. When I gave her the sign for &amp;#8216;eat&amp;#8217; and showed her the spoonful of baby food she opened her mouth like a little birdie. It was very cute. She did it until she got full or tired of the repetition. Watching her this past weekend I saw that she is starting to give signs of wanting but I don&amp;#8217;t think she knows she is doing it yet. Besides opening her mouth like a little bird, sheÃ‚Â definitelyÃ‚Â has moments when she only wants Momma :)Ã‚Â
  &lt;/p&gt;
  
  &lt;p&gt;
    Good weekend, great weather. We went for two &amp;#8216;hikes&amp;#8217; this weekend with Hannah. Last Saturday Julie and I got up early, went to breakfast at the farmers market on 11th St. Later we went up to the Bebaso trail/loop west of Boulder. Hannah first hike was fun. She fell asleep for the first half but was awake for the last mile or so.Ã‚Â On Sunday we went with Cory, Jen and Mason and walked around on the Boulder Creek Path. Both hikes were great little warmups and I look forward to some good backpacking with her.Ã‚Â
  &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>