<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mountains on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</title>
    <link>https://socalranch.land/tags/mountains/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mountains on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 17:05:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://socalranch.land/tags/mountains/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Copper Triangle</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-08-06-copper-triangle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 17:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-08-06-copper-triangle/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Besides building the split level addition to the deck I have had another summer project. Well, it is not really my project, I am just part of the support team. Julie trained (with Rob and Katie) all spring and summer for the Copper Triangle ride. This morning they all got up at 5am and rode ~80 miles over three mountain passes. Starting at Copper Mtn and finishing with a scenic downhill over Vail Pass they DID IT!. I am very proud.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What does support entail? Lots and lots of Hannah TIme. She helped me build the wall, go to the gym for yoga, mow the lawn and today take pictures and cheer riders on. We did a bit of cheering while waiting to see them ride by before climbing Vail Pass and she also did disagreeing with the situation. See, I thought I lost my wallet thursday and asked to have holds put on my bank card and credit card that I carry in it. Lucky for me A cop was nearby and took it to the property and evidence division in Boulder. Not so lucky for me is that it&amp;#8217;s a pain in the ass to unlock the cards so all&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>