<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>in5 on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</title>
    <link>https://socalranch.land/tags/in5/</link>
    <description>Recent content in in5 on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2011 08:36:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://socalranch.land/tags/in5/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Go Big or Go Home</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-08-12-go-big-or-go-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2011 08:36:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-08-12-go-big-or-go-home/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I just re-read what I put on the two pages bookending the &amp;#8220;Think Big&amp;#8221; two page spread in the in5 book. If I am not going to DO, why do I show up? To put it into a perspective that I have, lets talk riding. Riding anything, everything. I hope you like to ride as much as I do or at least have a passion for something that takes a mastery of your mind and your body in concert. For me thats where the soul lives. In the best rides, the lines that are the most fun are also the most challenging. Those are the sessions that force me to be &lt;em&gt;in the moment&lt;/em&gt; and I don&amp;#8217;t think. Once the trail is behind me I&amp;#8217;ll usually say to myself, &amp;#8220;Wow! That was fun.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Was it fun? That is the most important thing. Are the problems that you solve fun? If not, why do you wait for it to be fun &amp;#8211; make up a game for one. The volvo repair shop wants $850 to put in a new alternator and I can get it the same day. I would rather find something else to do with that money. So car repairs,&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting Up My Dreams</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-04-30-setting-up-my-dreams/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 01:04:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-04-30-setting-up-my-dreams/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your imagination is the preview to life&amp;#8217;s coming attractions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Albert Einstein&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have never written down my goals and usually [day]dream ideas and things I want to do when I am driving. Thats likely why I am only an average driver and make myself ignore the phone &amp;#8211; there is only so much processing power my brain can do at one time. There are several variations to the same themes in my daydreams &amp;#8211; snowboarding every day, solving interesting and profitable problems, migrating around the world with Julie to see and do fun things and showing Hannah the things I like to do and have found to be useful to know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the book they say when you write your dreams down they become goals. It isn&amp;#8217;t just writing them down though the most successful people review them on an ongoing basis. Perhaps the problem to be solved is two fold; first, my brain needs something concrete to focus on and second, in order to make progress towards my dreams (which are hazy and and ill defined patterns in my stream of thought) the dream needs to be refined as I understand it better, as I know myself better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are some of my recent&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mission</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-04-11-mission/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2011 08:41:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-04-11-mission/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The next part asks me to think about and determine my mission statement. Because of how I read I shortened it to mission and substitute focus in several places where that made more sense to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are a few inspirational quotes from famous and successful people and the book offers a few suggestions fo refining your own mission. For me that means I need to keep it short and concise &amp;#8211; focused. But I started out pretty verbose, rambling almost as a wrote a few paragraphs about all of my grandiose ideas over the years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I wrote, my mind wandered and focused on the people who are most important to me. This automatically associated my grand ideas with them and I ended up with lots of details. I deleted the details but retained the association of important people in my life with important things to do with and for them. As I re-worked the text it expanded and contracted and gave clues to the direction I want to travel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is my mission? I like to be creative. It doesn&amp;#8217;t matter if I am finding a fun line down the slope or trying to find an easier way to get&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Identify Your Value</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-02-28-identify-your-value/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 22:08:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-02-28-identify-your-value/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    The book starts off with a great line:
  &lt;/p&gt;
  
  &lt;blockquote&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;
      DECIDE WHATS NEXT IN YOUR LIFE AND STRATEGIZE HOW TO GET IT.
    &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  
  &lt;p&gt;
    I&amp;#8217;m not even sure if strategize is a word but the idea is both powerful and subtle. We always tell each other our greatest wants, if only. Most of my if only&amp;#8217;s don&amp;#8217;t require huge amounts of money. More than money they require time and flexibility. Ask a meterologist to predict the next snow storm he can&amp;#8217;t do it, not with high accuracy. He can run the models, know the climate and the different types of weather patterns; but they are wrong more often that they are right because weather is random, truly unpredictable. The storms never hit exactly when they are supposed to, they never have as much or as little as they are supposed to. As in Life. So if i can&amp;#8217;t predict whats next and life is random, how do I get my &amp;#8216;If only&amp;#8217;s when it&amp;#8217;s convenient for me?&amp;#8217;
  &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five Year Goal</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-02-20-five-year-goal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2011 19:18:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-02-20-five-year-goal/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am adding a new tag so that I can organize the things I have written down in the book Julie got me for Christmas.The name of the book is &amp;#8220;Five&amp;#8221; by Dan Zadra.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I went through it once to understand it and then again to record my details. Now it&amp;#8217;s time to publish them so I can track my progress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The book itself is a very nicely designed concept book. Through a thoughtful layout and color scheme it presents the tools that anyone has at their disposal to answering the question,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8220;Where will you be five years from today?&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The question and answer format is interesting; it forces the reader to focus inward for the answers. And as fond as I am of snowboarding the Vasquez Cirque by myself or gentle morning yoga sessions that focus more on the mind than the body; I do very little inward directed thought to answer questions. Most of questions can be answered with a quick web search. However, for questions like this, there is no way to Google an easy or quick answer. As I went through the exercises the first time one thing became apparent. I have become very dependent on internet search to answer my&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>