<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AtWork on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</title>
    <link>https://socalranch.land/categories/atwork/</link>
    <description>Recent content in AtWork on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2016 22:35:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://socalranch.land/categories/atwork/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>On Dumb Leadership</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2016-02-03-on-dumb-leadership/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2016 22:35:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2016-02-03-on-dumb-leadership/</guid>
      <description>Anyone can be a leader and everyone should lead something. We are all professionals and experts at the things we do most.
From what I see, the best leaders are always learning. They ask questions, teach them selves new things and effectively identify those in the next generation with the most fearless voices. The ones who are optimistic that anything can happen. Anything at all.&amp;nbsp;
As a parent I struggle to ride the line between efficiency and wading through all of the noise that my next generation emits and letting her explore and broadcast her way to where I need her to be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yosemite Bluettooth Connectivity Fix</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2015-05-15-yosemite-bluettooth-connectivity-fix/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 15:41:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2015-05-15-yosemite-bluettooth-connectivity-fix/</guid>
      <description>I have been having issues with my trackpad and bluetooth keyboard reconnecting to after I wake up from a sleep session. Only twice now but the same thing. Instead of restarting (which will fix it) you can drop into the command line and run these two commands:
  sudo kextunload -b com.apple.iokit.BroadcomBluetoothHostControllerUSBTransport
  sudo kextload -b com.apple.iokit.BroadcomBluetoothHostControllerUSBTransport
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Angular 101</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-06-24-angular-101/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2014 16:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-06-24-angular-101/</guid>
      <description>From Anatidae&amp;#8217;s comment on the web:
  If you&amp;#8217;re messing with the DOM, do it in a directive If you&amp;#8217;re modifying your data, do it in your controllers or services.  If you&amp;#8217;re defining data, do it in a factory.   Also, the faster you forget about jQuery, the faster you will be productive building an Angular app. You can always bring it back later if you still want to and you may run into in in disguise in one of your directives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Note To Self</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-06-22-note-to-self/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2014 00:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-06-22-note-to-self/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Or, career plans for the next two decades:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“One of the main ways to deliver education over the next 10 to 20 years is going to be through smartphones,” von Ahn says.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts About Content</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-05-15-thoughts-about-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2013 09:55:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-05-15-thoughts-about-content/</guid>
      <description>A reoccurring theme in any business is the marketing and &amp;#8216;systematic&amp;#8217; communication that needs to take place between a company and a customer. I have been working on something like this during the past sprint. Except that even with a complex system it is still manual to update the content, ie the message. Further complicating this is that as undesirable (IMO) as email is, it is still a requirement for customer outreach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That&amp;#8217;s Odd</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-04-03-thats-odd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2013 12:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-04-03-thats-odd/</guid>
      <description>These days I spend more time in Xcode with Objective-C than the web application part of my world. However the API needs to talk to the iOS app so I jump back into that world intermittently. I used to think JavaScript was my strongest language and that PHP was second.
No more! Today i modified the Objective-C code that interfaces to the API in a fraction of the time it took me to figure out how to change the API for this particular issue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advice From A Salesman</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-03-22-advice-from-a-salesman/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 15:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-03-22-advice-from-a-salesman/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Its a cold dark world. When you find a warm light, even a small flicker cup your hands around it and enjoy the warmth. Nurture it &amp;#8211; if its a candle and the wax is almost gone transfer it to a new candle so it can continue to add light to the world. Science, numbers, logic makes me feel warm because it is easy to internalize ones answer as right or wrong. The answer to the math question is either correct or incorrect or, the function you write has the correct output that you need or it doesn&amp;#8217;t. It doesn&amp;#8217;t matter how you got to the correct output. For most things in life and business, it only matters that you got to the correct answer for a particular problem. Solving any kind of problem &amp;#8211; even small and trivial ones always makes me feel warm inside and adds flicker to my flame.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently I have found myself in an odd position with a problem I am uneducated for and unprepared to solve. Selling my skill set and experience to a range of businesses with unique problems regarding the internet. I like the web and I want to work with web technology to&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seven Questions You Should Work Into An Interview</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-03-09-seven-questions-you-should-work-into-an-interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 09:33:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-03-09-seven-questions-you-should-work-into-an-interview/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Accepting a job offer from an unknown quantity has many consequences down the line on your career. Good managers/teams/companies will help you build up a network of assets and resources long after have moved up and on in your career. To look out for you long term career goals and aspirations you need to go beyond the &amp;#8220;I&amp;#8217;m willing to take any job or position that I am buzzword qualified for.&amp;#8221; You need to identify the best managers/teams and companies that are thinking about their long term vision and understand how new employees fit into that. Here are seven questions I will work into my future interviews for full time employment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why are you interested in Hiring me and what do you know about me?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Managers that truly have an interest in hiring the best person for the job will take the time to research their top candidates. They will do a google search for you, check you out on LinkedIn and consider the skills you have that can make their team or organization successful. Uninterested managers will either not consider you a top candidate and be interviewing you to meet an HR requirement or, they will be looking to associate your skills&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working With Excel Data</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-09-26-working-with-excel-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2011 14:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-09-26-working-with-excel-data/</guid>
      <description>Excel is blah to work with. A client gives us data made with it though and they put symbols in the text. After trying to cat out the tsv file I found this solution from within emacs:
M-x replace-regexp&amp;lt;br /&amp;gt; [[:nonascii:]] RET RET
It found and replaced the pesky tm symbols in the text file with nothing. I wonder if the [[:nonascii:]] char class is available on the command line in awk or sed?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Today&amp;#8217;s Bash Line</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-09-07-todays-bash-line/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2011 20:12:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-09-07-todays-bash-line/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;br /&amp;gt; find . -name &#39;dbconfig.js&#39; | xargs cat | grep sql&amp;lt;br /&amp;gt; 
I was looking for some examples of how other people updated the gears database with variables. This did the trick.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with sed and tabs</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-04-15-working-with-sed-and-tabs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2011 10:36:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-04-15-working-with-sed-and-tabs/</guid>
      <description>sed -i &amp;#8216;s/[&amp;#8211;TAB&amp;#8211;]/ /g&amp;#8217; file.txt
In place of --TAB-- , give CTRL + V followed by TAB.
&amp;nbsp;
http://www.atoztoa.com/2008/12/replace-tab-using-sed.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>redundant replication is the d&amp;#8230;</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-10-24-redundant-replication-is-the-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2008 09:58:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-10-24-redundant-replication-is-the-d/</guid>
      <description>redundant replication is the definition of tedious</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Busy Week</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-07-17-busy-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 13:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-07-17-busy-week/</guid>
      <description>Very busy this week. I did an AM Train on monday but haven&amp;#8217;t ridden since then. GOAL: make to the 1&amp;frasl;2 way point in under 4 hours!
When Julie is sick and Hannah can&amp;#8217;t have unlimited access to her momma, Hannah gets cranky. She is getting very curious about her environment, crawling around and trying to pull herself up on all kinds of things. I need to do the stair gates because she likes to climb.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>