<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Auto on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</title>
    <link>https://socalranch.land/categories/auto/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Auto on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 May 2009 12:44:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://socalranch.land/categories/auto/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Murano: New Front Brakes</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-05-24-murano-new-front-brakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2009 12:44:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-05-24-murano-new-front-brakes/</guid>
      <description>Mileage: 45212
Notes: replaced factory installed front brake pads with Wagner Thermo Quiet Ceramic brake pads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yea Day</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-03-07-yea-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2009 11:52:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-03-07-yea-day/</guid>
      <description>Busy morning. Got tons of stuff done 🙂
Changed the oil in the Murano. I&amp;#8217;ll drop off the used stuff on our way to the butterfly zoo later today but I still need to find a place for used oil filters.
Waxed poetic on my snowboard so I am ready for some speed runs down the cirque. I hope that the cornice drop is still at the top of the run I was riding a few weeks ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly ToDo&amp;#8217;s</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-02-17-weekly-todos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2009 09:35:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-02-17-weekly-todos/</guid>
      <description> Take Volvo in for service on wednesday Clean House  Bathrooms:Master, Hannahs, Downstairs Dust: bedrooms, Office, G5, Dowsnstairs Vacuum: Upstairs, Downstairs Kitchen: Countertops, sweep floor, mop floor  Sell back some Wii games and buy Mario Kart MERE: install wp software and plugins needed, set up the custom theme Pets: Ride BoBo three times, take pups for runs/walks three times Write 2 shell scripts Papa Mac Session with dad Home Depot for garden mods  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windshield Repair</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-10-29-windshield-repair/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2008 14:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-10-29-windshield-repair/</guid>
      <description>**UPDATE2** boulderwindshields.com was great, they showed up early at my work location and had it filled in about ten minutes. you can still see where the chip was, barely. Hopefully it won&amp;#8217;t crack any further.
**UPDATE** boulderwindshields.com looks promising: $59.95 for the first chip. $30 better than the online quote J got. I filled out their contact form and am waiting to hear back from them.Ã‚Â
Julie found an online quote of $99 to repair a windshield chip in the Murano.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend ToDo List</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-10-22-weekend-todo-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2008 15:45:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-10-22-weekend-todo-list/</guid>
      <description> Winterize Sprinkler System Fertilize Lawn Change Oil in Murano Take Volvo in for tire rotation Bring plants in from front porch Fall Pictures Horse swap sale &amp;#8211; looking for an easy to put on winter blanket for Bo take Hannah (the lion) to the Trunk or Treat (didn&amp;#8217;t go) price Murano tires at costco dog food @ Costco  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boxers @ Work</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-08-28-boxers-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2008 11:13:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-08-28-boxers-work/</guid>
      <description>I have the side yard (dog run) apart while I fill in the low areas of backfill around the foundation that has sunk. I am also putting a split rail fence, that T&amp;#8217;s off the fenceÃ‚Â separatingÃ‚Â our yard form the neighbors house, with a gate to seperate side yard from back yard. I&amp;#8217;ll also need to spread some some cover material that is not river rock. River rock is quite possibly the worst landscaping material I have ever seen or worked with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strange Night</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-07-25-strange-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 08:51:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-07-25-strange-night/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It was a strange feeling to go over the M&amp;amp;S&amp;#8217;s last night with Julie gone and myÃ‚Â parentsÃ‚Â watching Hannah. Hannah did great last night. WeÃ‚Â wentÃ‚Â through her usual routine of playing, eating, and shower. Since it was only 6:30 Papa Rosa and I went to the auto part store to get a new distributer cap andÃ‚Â rotorÃ‚Â thingy. Hannah came with us and took a light nap on the way there. The auto store woke her up though and she stayed awake until we got home. She wasn&amp;#8217;t quite all the way tired so Mom played with her till she put her to bed. She stayed down all night! It was reported to me yesterday that she can stand on her own and take three or four steps at a time all by herself. I&amp;#8217;ll have to get a video of that. I can maybe post it on the website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hannah woke up this morning is a very smiley mood. She drank her bottle in less than ten minutes and then started crawling all over me and looking at the animals. We got up and went downstairs to get breakfast ready and Momma Rosa made Papa Rosa feed Hannah. She&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>