<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Meetings on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</title>
    <link>https://socalranch.land/tags/meetings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Meetings on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2011 17:08:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://socalranch.land/tags/meetings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on leading a meeting</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-01-14-thoughts-on-leading-a-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2011 17:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-01-14-thoughts-on-leading-a-meeting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have been attending many meetings the past year. These are my unofficial guidelines to remember, hopefully they will help you host an effective and productive meeting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, create a compelling presentation. While I am not an expert on creating great presentations here are things I would recommend: Be direct with what you want to say, three word phrases or less. Your audience can scan the slide and then focus on you and what you are saying. The same goes for graphics &amp;#8211; make them simple to understand by pretending that you are creating it for the audience reading Time or Newsweek.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before you start into the presentation let the audience know that you are going to talk through the slides first and that you will open up/ lead discussion after you are finished talking. This will allow you to present the information you do have in bulk and then, during the discussion you can focus on the feedback your audience is giving back to you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During your presentation focus on a simple, clear message and use as few words as possible to convey meaningful information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plan. Depending on the audience, plan your presentation accordingly. If the meeting is an hour long try to condense&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>