<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Interviewing on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</title>
    <link>https://socalranch.land/tags/interviewing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Interviewing on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 09:33:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://socalranch.land/tags/interviewing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Seven Questions You Should Work Into An Interview</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-03-09-seven-questions-you-should-work-into-an-interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 09:33:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-03-09-seven-questions-you-should-work-into-an-interview/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Accepting a job offer from an unknown quantity has many consequences down the line on your career. Good managers/teams/companies will help you build up a network of assets and resources long after have moved up and on in your career. To look out for you long term career goals and aspirations you need to go beyond the &amp;#8220;I&amp;#8217;m willing to take any job or position that I am buzzword qualified for.&amp;#8221; You need to identify the best managers/teams and companies that are thinking about their long term vision and understand how new employees fit into that. Here are seven questions I will work into my future interviews for full time employment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why are you interested in Hiring me and what do you know about me?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Managers that truly have an interest in hiring the best person for the job will take the time to research their top candidates. They will do a google search for you, check you out on LinkedIn and consider the skills you have that can make their team or organization successful. Uninterested managers will either not consider you a top candidate and be interviewing you to meet an HR requirement or, they will be looking to associate your skills&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>