<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Toys on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</title>
    <link>https://socalranch.land/categories/toys/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Toys on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2015 01:09:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://socalranch.land/categories/toys/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Stirling Engine</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2015-01-08-stirling-engine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2015 01:09:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2015-01-08-stirling-engine/</guid>
      <description>This just got added to my wish list:
&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Train Gears In Slow Motion</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-12-08-train-gears-in-slo-motion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2014 01:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-12-08-train-gears-in-slo-motion/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Me</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-09-15-new-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2013 03:10:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-09-15-new-me/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;ve been using Procreate more and more. It is steadily replacing Paper by 53 as my go to app to sketch, mock or doodle. I don&amp;#8217;t know if it&amp;#8217;s the weird tone the support staff takes in papers forums (and the sad we&amp;#8217;re just like Apple and we know what&amp;#8217;s best for you attitude; without even knowing why Apple can get away with it and they can&amp;#8217;t) or the Pro part of Procreate: a free downloadable book for the manual, layers and I can import things into the app to draw on top of.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self Assembly</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-03-19-self-assembly/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 00:17:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-03-19-self-assembly/</guid>
      <description>Hannah had lots of fun at the Pincrest jump rope for the heart. They she has been using mine because the first one we got her didn&amp;#8217;t work as good as mine.
Yesterday we picked her out a new one and today she got a second one from school. Attached to it was this plane. She did the assembly all by herself on the ride home from school. Last Sunday I got to show her how the Volvo brakes come apart and go back together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camera Fund</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-10-28-camera-fund/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2008 11:09:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-10-28-camera-fund/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The supposedly waterproof movie camera was not so waterproof. I am in the process of either getting it repaired or reimbursed for it under the credit card warranty. I submitted the initial paperwork and need to check online to see what the status of it is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am also starting a camera fund so I can get a new movie/dlsr camera. I already know which model I want, &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.nikonusa.com/Find-Your-Nikon/Product/Digital-SLR/25446/D90.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;this one&lt;/a&gt;. Since it will take really good pictures and movies its the best of both worlds. One think I found with the movie camera is that I take alot of one to three minute clips that get edited together. Not being a movie, my life doesn&amp;#8217;t require &lt;sup&gt;24&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;7&lt;/sub&gt; filming to capture the memorable moments.Ã‚Â&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The strategy for having a camera fund is two fold:Ã‚Â&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I don&amp;#8217;t have $1500 cash lying around and I don&amp;#8217;t want to charge this purchase &amp;#8230;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;By the time the fund has enough money for the purchase the price may have come down because of new models, competition or a decent used model might be on craigslist.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to put a fund tracking widget on the splash page so I can track its progress with a graph/chart. Also, I could&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>