<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Uncategorized on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</title>
    <link>https://socalranch.land/categories/uncategorized/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Uncategorized on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 04:27:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://socalranch.land/categories/uncategorized/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ranch Life</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2017-03-31-ranch-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 04:27:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2017-03-31-ranch-life/</guid>
      <description>Even if its just a suburban ranch its still full of life and lessons and hard work. Surviving is more than just showing up. Thriving is more than waiting for nice pleasant things to show up.&amp;nbsp;
Having a plan. Sticking to it and chipping away at the mou Taib of work are two keys to fulfilling a dream come true on the urban ranch.&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Growing Fast Now</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2016-06-07-growing-fast-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 00:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2016-06-07-growing-fast-now/</guid>
      <description>I just deleted the calendar reminder I set to make sure I know when to leave to pick Hannah up.&amp;nbsp;
She is in fourth grade now. She is going to go to a new school next year. And, she has a new home now.&amp;nbsp;
Lyrics from Puscifer&amp;#8217;s Mamma Sed combined with Pink Floyd&amp;#8217;s Time come to mind but they aren&amp;#8217;t quite right.&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Structure for Investigation &amp;#038; Analysis</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2016-03-20-structure-for-investigation-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2016 14:28:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2016-03-20-structure-for-investigation-analysis/</guid>
      <description>ABSTRACT
The big picture and lay of the land today.&amp;nbsp;OBJECTIVE
What are you setting out to accomplish? What will you deliver as a final &amp;#8216;product.&amp;#8217;&amp;nbsp;
DESIGN, SETTING, SUBJECTS
Wha and how will the data be connected? Where will this collection take place and what are the conditions there? Who (or what) will the data be gathered from?
MAIN OUTCOMES &amp;amp; MEASURES (KPI)
How will you measure and summarize the body of data?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter Rules</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2015-12-27-harry-potter-rules/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2015 03:21:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2015-12-27-harry-potter-rules/</guid>
      <description>It is written that you must read all of the Harry Potter books before you can visit the Disney Harry Potter resort.&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How It Mixed</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2015-12-25-how-it-mixed/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2015 07:50:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2015-12-25-how-it-mixed/</guid>
      <description>Hannah was helping me make frosting today and I tried to get her to use the mixer. Because, you and I know it&amp;#8217;s faster. She kept saying no so, hey it xmas eve and there is no hurry.&amp;nbsp;
I probed a bit because it was obvious to me that the matchine was faster and more efficient at mixing the food coloring into the frosting. &amp;#8220;It does it to fast she said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Pumpkin Carving and Shopkins</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2015-10-26-halloween-pumpkin-carving-and-shopkins/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2015 04:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2015-10-26-halloween-pumpkin-carving-and-shopkins/</guid>
      <description>Hannah and I carved pumpkins today while Julie managed us. I had to turn off the helicopter parental instincts and let her rip on the horse. She shreds pretty well and did it all herself.&amp;nbsp;
Here is the video:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I imagine this is a key</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-04-04-i-imagine-this-is-a-key/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2014 05:22:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-04-04-i-imagine-this-is-a-key/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Wish It Knew</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-03-18-i-wish-it-knew/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2014 06:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-03-18-i-wish-it-knew/</guid>
      <description>I wish my fridge and other lighting fixtures knew that it was after 9:30pm and only turned on at 30% brightness. For that matter, you to iPad. You not to disturb me, why can&amp;#8217;t I tell you to be gentle with my eyes automagically after a set time?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chalk Time</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-03-14-chalk-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2014 01:37:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-03-14-chalk-time/</guid>
      <description>I like doing art with Hannah. She thinks I know what I&amp;#8217;m doing. All I do is fallback on the things I know and make the rest up as I go along.
Chalk is my favorite medium to play outside together with her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Having The Right Idea</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-03-11-having-the-right-idea/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2014 01:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-03-11-having-the-right-idea/</guid>
      <description>She already has the right idea. I just give her permission to make it her own for the first sentence. After that, her ideas roll onto the paper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Valentine</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-02-14-a-valentine/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 17:39:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-02-14-a-valentine/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Different Tree</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-01-26-a-different-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2014 16:48:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-01-26-a-different-tree/</guid>
      <description>I was inspired by our trip to Yosemite. Today&amp;#8217;s tree sketch is a sequoia silloetteish inky thing and fulfills the create something every day requirement even if I don&amp;#8217;t get to write the Clojure function that can parse metadata from an image file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pretty Dead End Points</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-01-25-pretty-dead-end-points/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 22:53:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-01-25-pretty-dead-end-points/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I wonder, should my app have pretty dead end points so that my user can find them self somewhere or with something that looks cool, pleases the eye with shiny distractions and does nothing function related to the app but entertains and delights and takes their mind down an unintended path for a few minutes?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 5am Doodle</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-01-17-the-5am-doodle/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 16:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-01-17-the-5am-doodle/</guid>
      <description>Hannah got up with me this morning and we started by drawing my usual tree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comment For Me</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-01-14-comment-for-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 06:20:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-01-14-comment-for-me/</guid>
      <description>I found myself replying to a conversation thread online and thought it was worth saving.
 Do you plan on having children? Will your grandchildren&amp;#8217;s grandchildren wonder where they came frome and what it was like?
If only I could query the daily activities and conversations of my great grandparents or query thousands of photos and movies for people, places and moments that my have been talked about when I was a child.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Put What Where?</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-01-12-put-what-where/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 03:36:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-01-12-put-what-where/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Thinking about an issue I need to solve for myself I started thing about all things free. Most things online are free, supported with marketing. All it requires is acceptance of Terms &amp;amp; Conditions be they what they may. This causes a problem. Not for me or you but for our grandchildren&amp;#8217;s grandchildren. They will never be able to access the accounts we blindly use with out thinking about the long term view and our relationship with the data we all create. I am company agnostic in this regard: they are all guilty of manipulation human nature for profit. And thats ok, for now. But what about my information a hundred years from now? The corporations won&amp;#8217;t care. I hope and try to parent to create a future generation that will care about the things I have learned and things that shaped and guided me and provided the vibrant color in my life. And if they do, how will the get glimpses of that color? Understand how some things in a hundred years are different to the point of alienation yet others remain as constant as the mountain top that beckons me to walk up and ride down.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Horrible</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-01-11-horrible/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2014 06:07:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-01-11-horrible/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;#8217;t believe it took me this long to watch Dr. Horrible&amp;#8217;s Sing Along Blogit&amp;#8217;s been in my Netflix list for a while now.
If you like Neil Patrick Harris and Nathan Filian tv shows it&amp;#8217;s worth the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Hannah</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-01-08-happy-hannah/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2014 12:32:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-01-08-happy-hannah/</guid>
      <description>A drawing of Hannah and Oreo ( Santa&amp;#8217;s helper rat ). I&amp;#8217;m filing this one under the, this is worth remembering because I found it by accident, was impressed with its form and love the smile on her face.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creation Is Easy</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-01-03-creation-is-easy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2014 04:38:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-01-03-creation-is-easy/</guid>
      <description>Anyone can create something out of nothing. All you have to do is get the bad prototypes out of the way first and fast. Here is a tree:
&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunday Night Clay Design Session</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-01-02-sunday-night-clay-design-session/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 15:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2014-01-02-sunday-night-clay-design-session/</guid>
      <description>The project we came up with was to design a flag using colored construction paper and play doh. Mine turned into more of an icon and Hannah&amp;#8217;s was imported to Procreate for some graphical fine tuning and pixel clean up.
Hannah:

Me:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2014 Todo</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-12-30-2014-todo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 18:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-12-30-2014-todo/</guid>
      <description>There are three things I will finish this year:
1) The Story that has need rolling around my head all these years ( mashulg, silent guild &amp;amp; the mellonheads)
2) The Song that exists only in my head and when I play it for Hannah AND the Xmas song for next year with extempore
3) The Images &amp;#8211; the pictures that complement both The Story and The Song need to graduate from doodles into finished files.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elf Rose</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-12-17-elf-rose/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2013 23:35:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-12-17-elf-rose/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EOY:NY Site Goals</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-12-12-eoy-site-goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 16:38:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-12-12-eoy-site-goals/</guid>
      <description>Five things to do for this site:
 Add a better font and update the favicon Add an icomoon graphic Write eoy/new year post Add some visual style/color Update the version control on DO Server Splash Page w/ hg-service and some subtle animations my api page + angular interface  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AM Fishing</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-10-30-am-fishing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 15:49:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-10-30-am-fishing/</guid>
      <description>I had a minor issue this morning with my work computer. It&amp;#8217;s set up with OSX Mavericks and I use two external monitors. The most anticipated feature I was looking for was the real support for full screen modes on multiple monitors and I have been making heavy use of it. Since I work in a PCI compliant environment I have a five minute time out that locks the system and also requires a password when waking up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When I Fall</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-10-05-when-i-fall/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2013 17:55:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-10-05-when-i-fall/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/20131005-110045.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/20131005-110045.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;20131005-110045.jpg&#34; class=&#34;alignnone size-full&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do not base the measurement of myself on the number of times that I have fallen. I measure myself on two things: what was I doing when I fell and how did I get up.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yart Today</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-10-05-yart-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2013 15:45:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-10-05-yart-today/</guid>
      <description>Yart is short for yard art of course. Hannah helped me clean up detritus from the Santa Ana winds yesterday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advice For Getting Started With GIT And Angular</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-09-07-advice-for-getting-started-with-git-and-angular/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2013 22:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-09-07-advice-for-getting-started-with-git-and-angular/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;First, clone an existing project, don&amp;#8217;t inherit a project from github thats actively developed by someone smarter than you instead of an overseas contractor who was also learning Angular for the first time 😉&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go Tangent to the Full Circle</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-10-16-go-tangent-to-the-full-circle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2010 12:26:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-10-16-go-tangent-to-the-full-circle/</guid>
      <description>I remember the first time I downloaded python and did something with it. I don&amp;#8217;t remember exactly what it was but I recall setting up a loop and calculating something for a long list of numbers, data collected in the lab. It was fun and got me my answer quickly and I did not have to muddle through the confusing Excel interface to find the function that would do what I wanted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hannah&amp;#8217;s Birthday</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-10-13-hannahs-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2010 20:54:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-10-13-hannahs-birthday/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today she is three. I took the day off and we went down to the Denver Children&amp;#8217;s Museum. We got there when it opened and I think we got to all of the activities, some of them twice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was the fire truck, of course. And then we did a bit of shopping at the grocers after we did some construction. There were crayon rubbings and tree house tunnels and we used the words and shapes magnets for a while. Even I made some fun sentences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We had snacks and then surveyed the outside playground. Hannah could do three of the monkey bars by herself! Then we went back inside and did some more construction and attended to some animals in the vet clinic and headed home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Got home a little after one and she slept for an hour and a half. Then when she woke up she had a melt down because her peanut butter and nubutella sandwitch wasn&amp;#8217;t evenly distributed when she peeled the slices of bread apart. both the pb and nubutella ended up on one piece. I cannot describe how traumatic this i for a three year old. It must be experienced. After assesing the situation I recommended that she&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I don&amp;#8217;t think it does</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-05-23-i-dont-think-it-does/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2010 15:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-05-23-i-dont-think-it-does/</guid>
      <description>Wrode our bikrs to Bobo and put Hannah in the bike trailer. After we rode him up by the dump we sat.in the field and let him munch. Hannah and Julie were sitting down while Hannah tried to put her new pink helmet on julie.
She came to the conclusion: I think it&amp;#8217;s to big.
Oh girl, you are thinking now. 🙂</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>this Long</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-05-22-this-long/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2010 19:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-05-22-this-long/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;#8217;t believe it took me this long to find it. The trail system over by 128 &amp;amp; 93 is a fun ride. It doest have the length of Big Sycamore Cyn.
It was windy today, but that made the 90Ã‚Â</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A DVD feature I could do without</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-05-18-a-dvd-feature-i-could-do-without/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2010 19:55:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-05-18-a-dvd-feature-i-could-do-without/</guid>
      <description>The &amp;#8216;feature&amp;#8217; that disables my remote from skipping the ad for blue ray.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lightning in the Clouds</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-05-17-lightning-in-the-clouds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2010 20:01:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-05-17-lightning-in-the-clouds/</guid>
      <description>after a very sunny sprin.g day there wasightning in the forming clouds. It reminded me of heat lighnting on hot muggy Ohio nights.
It&amp;#8217;s breezy and 63 degrees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annual Balloon Launch</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-05-16-annual-balloon-launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2010 19:21:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-05-16-annual-balloon-launch/</guid>
      <description>Busy is the word of the day.
Up at six to see the balloons. A great spring morning. After brunch I pushed the mower around the yard. I think Julie is right about the backyard. I will be interested in what they propose.
We met Erica and Jeff in Denver for the rocky&amp;#8217;s game. Hannah was pretty tolerant of all the running around. We got home early and Julie was not feeling well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazing</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-05-11-amazing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2010 19:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-05-11-amazing/</guid>
      <description>the Pandora application is amazing.
The weather today is cold and rainy. Overcast with a chance of snow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mama Roosters</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-05-09-mama-roosters/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2010 19:02:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-05-09-mama-roosters/</guid>
      <description>I just said night night to mama roosters. I&amp;#8217;m still not sure how she talked me into that one.
Bedtime is such a magical time for a two year old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Different But Good</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-05-08-different-but-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2010 19:58:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-05-08-different-but-good/</guid>
      <description>I got a new phone today.
It came down to
 cost keyboard connectivity (with out computer)  So far the pre has been easy to use and set up. I like it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Head First</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-03-03-head-first/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2010 16:58:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-03-03-head-first/</guid>
      <description>nice weather. fun times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>the main frame</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-10-12-the-main-frame/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2009 14:45:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-10-12-the-main-frame/</guid>
      <description>Open the pod bay doors, HAL.
&amp;#8230;
Pod bay dors are open &amp;#8211; Have Fun!
I love it, an interesting challenge that would have been fun to do back in school. Its still fun now. The c programming is very strange. Thank goodness for javascript.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MS [intros]pection</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-10-06-ms-introspection/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2009 09:54:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-10-06-ms-introspection/</guid>
      <description>Re-learning to type well. a chance to improve my emacs habits.
how to learn to use help better.
how to use typing more effectively.
bigger picture ideas:
loss of functionality in my personal life
thoughts of mortality
what makes me happy
best things
worst things</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rehab</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-10-03-rehab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2009 22:04:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-10-03-rehab/</guid>
      <description>Started doing something instead of lying down.
Started steroids on friday. It makes me feel kinda wired. Gives me a head ache.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Almost 2</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-10-02-almost-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2009 23:35:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-10-02-almost-2/</guid>
      <description>She is almodt two.i can tell, i evn hear her whine about &amp;#8216;mine&amp;#8217;. In her dreams at night
I wondery why they all seem to pick it up the samerim?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hupdates</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-08-23-hupdates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2009 08:48:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-08-23-hupdates/</guid>
      <description>1) Hannah can now climb into her crib by herself. Its only a matter of time until she can also climb out.
2) Counting up to 15 (with a little help)
3) can sing the abc song, twinkle twinkle little star, ring around the rosies, baby bumble bee
4) repeats anything you say pretty accuratly
5) says &amp;#8216;i love _____&amp;#8217;, gives kisses ans hugs.
6) has three out of four molars in.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>