<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pets on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</title>
    <link>https://socalranch.land/tags/pets/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pets on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 May 2012 18:05:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://socalranch.land/tags/pets/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>High Ringbone</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-05-09-high-ringbone/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2012 18:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2012-05-09-high-ringbone/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;No, it&amp;#8217;s not a new drug. As we get Bobo ready to travel, we had a few things checked out. You know the things that you have happened and seemed little or odd but have corrected themselves with some rest a time? We have noticed Bobo being sore since Decemberish. I think that was that last time I remember Julie riding him. He has always been sore after being trimmed and there have been a few times when he was to sore to ride. So when the vet that did his Coggins test and other things said he was worried about foundering Julie took notice. Me, I don&amp;#8217;t know much about what that means as I married into horses and am learning as I go. Here are my notes about High Ringbone and what is means for Mr. Bobo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This morning the farrier, who gave me an excellent crash course into the physics of horse hoof anatomy, told me that he suspected Bobo had arthritis and it was causing High ringbone &amp;#8211; in my layman and unscientific terms is ossification around the top of his pastern bones that causes spurs to form in the front and on the sides where the joint&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gurgi&amp;#8217;s Last Day</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-10-16-gurgis-last-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2011 12:45:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-10-16-gurgis-last-day/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It was a cool crisp fall day. The storms of the day before had moved of to the east. We got up early with the sunrise and had a simple breakfast. Toast for me and scrambled eggs, turkey bacon and grilled chicken for you. Sitting around is never good for the soul so we went out to Mr BoBo. Hannah rode in the arena and you and Whitney chased him for a bit, like you always do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We came back home and I took care of a few things around the house. Once I got done I joined you and Whitney out on the deck with my guitar. You sat in the sun the way you always did. Upright on your haunches you enjoyed the view across the valley all the way over to the mountains. I don&amp;#8217;t know if it&amp;#8217;s just boxers but when you sat there stoically and sweetly it just killed me that you were in such dire straits. As I played the song you came over to sit next to me and sniffed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since it was my birthday and the best wife ever was going to a rock show (Foo Fighters) with me, we set you&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Fishys</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-09-15-new-fishys/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2011 07:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-09-15-new-fishys/</guid>
      <description>Hannah helped me pick out some new fish last night. Mr. Fishy died a few weeks ago when the tank had an oxygenation issue.
Since it was book club night Hannah and I had Mac n&amp;#8217; Cheese and then went to the pet store. She looked at all the fish but was more interested in the cats. She didn&amp;#8217;t want to choose I guided her into the Black Mollies and the Neon Tetras.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>