<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Riding on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</title>
    <link>https://socalranch.land/categories/riding/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Riding on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2013 17:55:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://socalranch.land/categories/riding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>When I Fall</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-10-05-when-i-fall/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2013 17:55:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-10-05-when-i-fall/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/20131005-110045.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/20131005-110045.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;20131005-110045.jpg&#34; class=&#34;alignnone size-full&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do not base the measurement of myself on the number of times that I have fallen. I measure myself on two things: what was I doing when I fell and how did I get up.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Favorite Things</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-08-25-10-favorite-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 06:39:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-08-25-10-favorite-things/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#8217;m sure this will change with time. Here is my list of 10 favorite things. (prompted by the &lt;a href=&#34;https://uncommon.cc&#34;&gt;uncommon&lt;/a&gt; website)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Letting Go</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-01-21-letting-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2013 14:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2013-01-21-letting-go/</guid>
      <description>Letting go is the hardest parental job to do. Last year we stopped using the ski reigns on Hannah while going down the slopes. The snowboard line is very different from the skiers line &amp;#8211; especially at slow speeds. IT got to be a lot of work but I still didn&amp;#8217;t want to let go. Finally, on a jbar hill with mama in back I just had her follow me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Copper Triangle</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-08-06-copper-triangle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 17:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-08-06-copper-triangle/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Besides building the split level addition to the deck I have had another summer project. Well, it is not really my project, I am just part of the support team. Julie trained (with Rob and Katie) all spring and summer for the Copper Triangle ride. This morning they all got up at 5am and rode ~80 miles over three mountain passes. Starting at Copper Mtn and finishing with a scenic downhill over Vail Pass they DID IT!. I am very proud.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What does support entail? Lots and lots of Hannah TIme. She helped me build the wall, go to the gym for yoga, mow the lawn and today take pictures and cheer riders on. We did a bit of cheering while waiting to see them ride by before climbing Vail Pass and she also did disagreeing with the situation. See, I thought I lost my wallet thursday and asked to have holds put on my bank card and credit card that I carry in it. Lucky for me A cop was nearby and took it to the property and evidence division in Boulder. Not so lucky for me is that it&amp;#8217;s a pain in the ass to unlock the cards so all&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World Top</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-02-12-world-top/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2011 00:59:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-02-12-world-top/</guid>
      <description>The world is spinning and we are falling down the slope. Here are some pictures of before I took the plunge.
In the one picture I am getting ready to eat lunch on top of the world. The other is black snow left over after they did avalanche control. It was surprisingly fresh and bouncy after I dropped onto it.
    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Early Season Loop</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-01-24-early-season-loop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2011 21:29:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2011-01-24-early-season-loop/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Before the storms roll through and they open up the back part of Vasquez Cirque, there is a loop that will provide all the powder and trees that I want. And it is only an hour and a half from my front door. Once you get there you can relax and enjoy the ride, the loop automatically repeats until only the base case is left.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is what you need to know:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should be comfortable on packed or powder. Moguls will be fun for you and you connect more turns than you miss. Trees are good, less people go there and the snow stays soft and the sound is muted. You are comfortable with the Cirque and the high speed (50-60 mph) run out down to the tree line.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take Pano Express and start down the catwalk. Take your time, everyone is going fast so they can make the traverse. We will not be going that far. Keep your eyes peeled riders left and take the turn off to Bella Fourche.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are listening to something good, turn in up and head down the path. After you pass the snow fences, look for your line between the trees. Keep your eyes peeled, there&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh St Helen</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-05-04-oh-st-helen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 18:46:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-05-04-oh-st-helen/</guid>
      <description>if Mt St. Helens ever went cold enough for snow to collect it looks like a great back country bowl to ride.
I am watching NOVA and it infotms me that it erupted in 2007 but it was nore of a fizzle. then the seismic activity went quit. Cool.
it was warm today. Sunny with strong winds out of the north.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Early Ride</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-05-02-early-ride/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2010 08:54:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-05-02-early-ride/</guid>
      <description>I had an interesting conversation with Hannah last night. When i went back into her room she was sitting on the rocker with some books.
She told me that she was sitting on her rocker reading but we could share it. I asked her what she wanted and found out that she likes to play with her friend mommy and she likes green eggs and ham. She also has two friends at school, Shaye and Emma.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CCT &amp;#8211; I Found Mud</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-04-25-cct-i-found-mud/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2010 12:48:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-04-25-cct-i-found-mud/</guid>
      <description>i started at the parking lot of my new job. behind the parking lot, there was a trail. i wanted to see where it came out. it exits on 119th and that means i can easily ride to work.
it was partly sunny and cool, around 60 degrees, but windy; so i rode up the the coal creek trail and took that until it ended up behind a golf course. along the way there was quite a bit of mud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Funny Thing</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-06-29-funny-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2009 10:26:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-06-29-funny-thing/</guid>
      <description>We stopped at the outlets on our way home from the lilac circle Breckenridge weekend. Hannah was sound asleep when we got out of the car. I carried her into the first store and she heard the music, opened her eyes and started bobbing her head to the music for a minute. Then she closed her eyes and snuggled back down into my shoulder, fast asleep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heil One</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-06-20-heil-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2009 16:36:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-06-20-heil-one/</guid>
      <description>Had a gentle second ride on my mountain bike this season. They did a good job with the improvements. I haven&amp;#8217;t ridden the loop part up top so that was fun, and a bit rocky. The meadows were still very green. It&amp;#8217;s almost like being back in Ohio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sitting Here Stopped</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-06-03-sitting-here-stopped/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2009 15:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-06-03-sitting-here-stopped/</guid>
      <description>I miss riding my mountain bike to work. I am not talking about the crappy bike lane commute into boulder. I miss the ride from the Moorepark trailhead to Amgen in Thousand Oaks.
It took about 45 min, had showers when I got there and I usually had the trail to lonesome.
Time is a luxury that I didn&amp;#8217;t realize I had until I started to run out of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And Then Some (more snow)</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-04-19-and-then-some/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2009 12:07:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-04-19-and-then-some/</guid>
      <description>Today is April
Riding three feet high and more
Thoughts of my two girls</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Pow Pow</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-04-05-spring-pow-pow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2009 10:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-04-05-spring-pow-pow/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;wp-content/uploads/2009/04/img_0131.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://192.241.192.98/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/img_0131-300x225.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Sun Tree&#34; title=&#34;Sun Behind Tree with Snow&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;225&#34; class=&#34;size-medium wp-image-914&#34; srcset=&#34;http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/img_0131-300x225.jpg 300w, http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/img_0131-768x576.jpg 768w, http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/img_0131-1024x768.jpg 1024w, http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/img_0131.jpg 1600w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;wp-content/uploads/2009/04/img_0129.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://192.241.192.98/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/img_0129-300x225.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Certainty Rocks&#34; title=&#34;Certainty Rocks&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;225&#34; class=&#34;size-medium wp-image-913&#34; srcset=&#34;http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/img_0129-300x225.jpg 300w, http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/img_0129-768x576.jpg 768w, http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/img_0129-1024x768.jpg 1024w, http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/img_0129.jpg 1600w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;wp-content/uploads/2009/04/img_0126.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://192.241.192.98/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/img_0126-300x225.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Untouched Snow in the Trees&#34; title=&#34;Untouched Snow in the Trees&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;225&#34; class=&#34;size-medium wp-image-912&#34; srcset=&#34;http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/img_0126-300x225.jpg 300w, http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/img_0126-768x576.jpg 768w, http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/img_0126-1024x768.jpg 1024w, http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/img_0126.jpg 1600w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;wp-content/uploads/2009/04/img_0123.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://192.241.192.98/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/img_0123-300x225.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Pillow Rock&#34; title=&#34;Pillow Rock&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;225&#34; class=&#34;size-medium wp-image-911&#34; srcset=&#34;http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/img_0123-300x225.jpg 300w, http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/img_0123-768x576.jpg 768w, http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/img_0123-1024x768.jpg 1024w, http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/img_0123.jpg 1600w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are birds chirping and I hear some muted &amp;#8220;whoo hoo&amp;#8217;s&amp;#8221; in the trees. There are 2-4 foot drifts in the trees and some thigh high drifts up on top of Vasquez Cirque. Yummy! The next run is Certainty and the ridge that gets the most snow, at least that&amp;#8217;s what I think.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It certainly did. I opted out of dropping off the cornice that forms on the left side of the run for the grove of trees and really big rocks on the right. Up top the un-tracked powder was thigh high at least. When the slope is that steep the turns are so smooth and easy it doesn&amp;#8217;t feel like turning on a snowboard. Once I got below the trees to where the rocks form a narrow gully, about ten feet wide I stopped to pick my line. Between the two largest rocks there is a nice channel that drops left, back into the Certainty slope and I had a very fast run out in the powder field below where I got some more beautiful turns. Then, below the next ridge, down underneath the tree line it was good, really good. Its a lot of work to get over there&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saturday Ride</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-03-28-saturday-ride/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2009 12:52:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-03-28-saturday-ride/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nice day, good weather. I got two nice drops into Vasquez Cirque. It was a little bumpy but there were still some calf/knee high patches and some decent turns leading into them. I need to think about dropping in less, unless I plan on going down one of the rocky chutes, I noticed that my turns feel more natural when I am reacting to the conditions of THIS turn rather than thinking about the next turn or the last turn or the really big rock that is coming up fast.Ã‚Â VisualizationÃ‚Â is still good at the top, it gives me a game plan but plans don&amp;#8217;t always turn out as you would expect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Got two runs down the baby park, popped some nice mellow airs on the baby five footers and the little rails and boxes are always fun. The biggest surprise was the carving and turns on my way back to winter park parking lot. I leaned into some gorgous s-turns and got really good extension both toe side and heel side. There was a bit of corn on the way down too, spring is fast approaching (the last week of weather aside). The last three weekends should be great for&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greener Grass Symptoms</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-03-14-greener-grass-symptoms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2009 11:13:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-03-14-greener-grass-symptoms/</guid>
      <description>It must be getting close to spring. Riding conditions were not ideal this morning. The Cirque was crusty and icy in places. Not at all like after a fresh snowfall. I hikes it once and then did a few groomer runs but carving was hard; there were to many people to carry speed through the turns safely.
Last week I watched some of re Mammoth videos from after their monster storm last month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Vasquez Cirque</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-03-12-more-vasquez-cirque/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2009 08:24:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-03-12-more-vasquez-cirque/</guid>
      <description>Good weather, no crowds and steep drops into powder and trees. Oh what fun.The whole ridge is open for business Organic snow shapes at the top of Vasquez Cirque The ridge looks untouched form this point of view during on of my hikes.  I made this 🙂</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coppery Taste</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-03-06-coppery-taste/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2009 17:22:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-03-06-coppery-taste/</guid>
      <description>Riding up the connector trail I had the coppery metallic taste of blood in my throat. It&amp;#8217;s an ok trail but a little to sandy for me.
I went around twice and my lungs felt better at the top. I am looking forward to riding the heil + hall trail in a few weeks when late spring hits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Powder Day</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-02-20-personal-powder-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2009 15:08:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-02-20-personal-powder-day/</guid>
      <description>Like a mental health day but with way more soul.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mmmm 4 Inches</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-02-15-mmmm-4-inches/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2009 18:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-02-15-mmmm-4-inches/</guid>
      <description>Rode up at Winterpark today with Jean-Francois. He rode to, no tellys for him today.
We started off in the fresh pow of Eagle Wind until they stopped blasting the Vasquez Circque. The mile+ hike is totally worth it. I haven&amp;#8217;t been on steeps like that since the Mammoth days and this was way less tracked because of the hiking required.
On the way home, he said we had to stop in Idaho Springs and get something called a &amp;#8216;mountain pie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bear Lake Snowboarding</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-02-02-bear-lake-snowboarding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2009 10:05:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-02-02-bear-lake-snowboarding/</guid>
      <description>Had a great day at the RMNP Bear Lake trail system. The only things missing were Julie and Hannah, but I think they might of been a little cold. This picture is of me hiking up to get some turns. Given my limited back country experience it was the first time in a long time that my heart rate was already going even before I dropped in, and, I only hiked halfway up the slope pictured in this picture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Powder Daze</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-01-26-powder-daze/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 08:51:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-01-26-powder-daze/</guid>
      <description>By Sunday morning, WInterpark had over two feet of fresh powder. I spent the morning riding Parsens bowl until that got really tracked up and the lift line got long. Then I made my way down the catwalk to Eagle Wind and rode in the trees till it closed. I found some thigh high stashes but most of it was mid calf or knee high.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WP 1</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-01-04-wp-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2009 10:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-01-04-wp-1/</guid>
      <description>Well the truck made it to Mary Jane but it&amp;#8217;s cold up here, about -4 at 9:30am. Hopefully she&amp;#8217;ll start for me when she cools back down 🙂
Thoughts I had on the way up:
Blender a spindrop logo. A raindrop clear bit colored with a hint of rainbow on it&amp;#8217;s surface and slightly twisted. Around the drop there is an orange halo spinning.
The truck made it home. Had a good 3 hour session.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finally, A Decent Ride Close to Home</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-10-04-finally-a-decent-ride-close-to-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2008 11:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-10-04-finally-a-decent-ride-close-to-home/</guid>
      <description>Riding new trails is always fun, at least the first time. Owen and I rode the new connector trail at Heil Ranch. Not extremely steep but a good fun trail. There are some rocky parts that can be a little technical. The speed up, slow down technical to keep your balance. There were some nice fast lines on the new connector trail to. And then coming down back to the Heil Ranch parking lot was fast and bumpy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AM Train</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-06-04-am-train/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2008 08:45:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-06-04-am-train/</guid>
      <description>Felt Good this AM. Didn&amp;#8217;t get passed but I didn&amp;#8217;t see any pros out there either.
Trip Dist: 18.62
Trip TIme: 1:09:59
Avg. Speed: 15.96
Max. Speed: 34.00
Thought about Vegas. I want to go to the WSOP 10K Seven Card Stud event that the RIO is hosting on Saturday. It starts at 5:00 pm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last Friday</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-06-03-last-friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2008 08:44:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-06-03-last-friday/</guid>
      <description>I forgot to post my stats from last Friday.
Total Distance: ~40
Average Speed: ~16
Total Time: 2:20 minutes.
I remember for some reason I was slow. Prolly because of the heat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saturday AM Ride</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-05-24-saturday-am-ride/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2008 11:59:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-05-24-saturday-am-ride/</guid>
      <description>Stats:
Trip Dist; 59.13
Trip Time: 3:31:52
Avg Speed: 16.74
Max Speed: 34.90
Description: Started with the Anthem loop and went up County Rd 7 past Highway 52. Took the first road left that was paved and ended up on County Rd 1. Headed back south on it and rode to Highway seven. Then I did it again The second lap was windy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saturday Morning Training</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-05-18-saturday-morning-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2008 12:43:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-05-18-saturday-morning-training/</guid>
      <description>Went for a training ride around Anthem and Vista Ridge this morning. Started out on a little loop. But ehen I came around by Bo&amp;#8217;s stable I decided to keep going up to highway 52. Over to county line road and then back through Anthem turned my ride into a big loop. I did a second smaller loop for good measure and made it back home before ten am.Ã‚Â
Ride Stats</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick AM Ride</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-03-05-quick-am-ride/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 10:36:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-03-05-quick-am-ride/</guid>
      <description>It was snowing today. Not to much, just a few inches but it was cold outside so I decided to go to the Gym. Getting up at 5:15 is no to hard once your body is moving. After quickly going through my weights routine I headed over to the stationary bike. After last Friday it made me feel nostalgic for Ventura County&amp;#8217;s weather.
On a stationary bike I just set the resistance and started peddling.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>