<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mountain Biking on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</title>
    <link>https://socalranch.land/categories/mountain-biking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mountain Biking on SoCal Ranch - a (sub)urban ranching experiment in organic and digital life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 May 2010 08:54:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://socalranch.land/categories/mountain-biking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Early Ride</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-05-02-early-ride/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2010 08:54:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-05-02-early-ride/</guid>
      <description>I had an interesting conversation with Hannah last night. When i went back into her room she was sitting on the rocker with some books.
She told me that she was sitting on her rocker reading but we could share it. I asked her what she wanted and found out that she likes to play with her friend mommy and she likes green eggs and ham. She also has two friends at school, Shaye and Emma.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CCT &amp;#8211; I Found Mud</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-04-25-cct-i-found-mud/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2010 12:48:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2010-04-25-cct-i-found-mud/</guid>
      <description>i started at the parking lot of my new job. behind the parking lot, there was a trail. i wanted to see where it came out. it exits on 119th and that means i can easily ride to work.
it was partly sunny and cool, around 60 degrees, but windy; so i rode up the the coal creek trail and took that until it ended up behind a golf course. along the way there was quite a bit of mud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Funny Thing</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-06-29-funny-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2009 10:26:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-06-29-funny-thing/</guid>
      <description>We stopped at the outlets on our way home from the lilac circle Breckenridge weekend. Hannah was sound asleep when we got out of the car. I carried her into the first store and she heard the music, opened her eyes and started bobbing her head to the music for a minute. Then she closed her eyes and snuggled back down into my shoulder, fast asleep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heil One</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-06-20-heil-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2009 16:36:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-06-20-heil-one/</guid>
      <description>Had a gentle second ride on my mountain bike this season. They did a good job with the improvements. I haven&amp;#8217;t ridden the loop part up top so that was fun, and a bit rocky. The meadows were still very green. It&amp;#8217;s almost like being back in Ohio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sitting Here Stopped</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-06-03-sitting-here-stopped/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2009 15:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-06-03-sitting-here-stopped/</guid>
      <description>I miss riding my mountain bike to work. I am not talking about the crappy bike lane commute into boulder. I miss the ride from the Moorepark trailhead to Amgen in Thousand Oaks.
It took about 45 min, had showers when I got there and I usually had the trail to lonesome.
Time is a luxury that I didn&amp;#8217;t realize I had until I started to run out of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coppery Taste</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-03-06-coppery-taste/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2009 17:22:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2009-03-06-coppery-taste/</guid>
      <description>Riding up the connector trail I had the coppery metallic taste of blood in my throat. It&amp;#8217;s an ok trail but a little to sandy for me.
I went around twice and my lungs felt better at the top. I am looking forward to riding the heil + hall trail in a few weeks when late spring hits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finally, A Decent Ride Close to Home</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-10-04-finally-a-decent-ride-close-to-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2008 11:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-10-04-finally-a-decent-ride-close-to-home/</guid>
      <description>Riding new trails is always fun, at least the first time. Owen and I rode the new connector trail at Heil Ranch. Not extremely steep but a good fun trail. There are some rocky parts that can be a little technical. The speed up, slow down technical to keep your balance. There were some nice fast lines on the new connector trail to. And then coming down back to the Heil Ranch parking lot was fast and bumpy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ten Minutes To Late :(</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-07-23-ten-minutes-to-late/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 09:14:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-07-23-ten-minutes-to-late/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Silver Rush MTB race was fun but I didn&amp;#8217;t finish. Grrr, I am annoyed with myself for taking to many breaks. I got to the &lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; way point in 4 hours and 10 minutes and the cutoff time was four hours. Next year besides the AM Train I will need to ride the HA (High Altitude) Train alot more. I plan on going up to the colorado trail between Frisco and Breckenridge and doing that as an out and back. It won&amp;#8217;t be fifty miles but it should be close to forty and its at a decently high altitude. Riding or pushing a bike at 11,000+ feet is pretty hard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hannah news; she is waving, almost saying Hi and crawling with a peg leg. She uses one leg to crawl like normal and the other leg is used with the foot flat on the ground to propel her around. She is pretty quick when she seesÃ‚Â somethingÃ‚Â she wants to go after like Momma, the dogs food dishes or the Bella the cat. Her legs are getting a bit of balance in them. I have seen her stand up unassisted, with no hands, for almost 20-30 seconds and she is taking&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Her Latest Trick</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-07-14-her-latest-trick/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2008 08:25:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-07-14-her-latest-trick/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hannahs MOST FUN THING TO DO, lately, has been to pull herself up on something and then let go. She flaps her arms like a bird and tries to balance on two legs. The longest she can balance is for 10 &amp;#8211; 15 seconds. She is also starting to look at other objects that she can balance on and edge her self close to them. I can see her thinking, &amp;#8220;I&amp;#8217;ll bet I can run to that before I fall!&amp;#8221; A little birdie is telling me that she will be walking before to long.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She is also started saying &amp;#8220;OH!&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes it is after we tell her &amp;#8220;NO!&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its kinda funny. We are still workign on some basic signs with her: Eat, More, No, gentle Mamma and Pappa. Nothing back yet but I think she might be starting to get the communicaiton thing. She is sleeping well. What is working now is that she will go down with Julie around 8:30 &amp;#8211; 9:00 and then I&amp;#8217;ll take her into her crib when I come to bed, later. For the last few days she has been sleeping through the night until about 5:45am or so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I logged about 120 miles last week, mostly on the AM&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hannah Crawls</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-07-07-hannah-crawls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2008 11:05:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-07-07-hannah-crawls/</guid>
      <description>Hannah started crawling for real this past weekend. It will be soon that she is standing up and running from support object to support object. She is getting also getting very vocal and has started to not like to sleep through the night 🙁
I did a training ride on Saturday, 25 miles on the colorado trail. I started from the Gold Hill Mine trailhead and went clockwise (if you are lookign east.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sycamore Canyon in February</title>
      <link>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-03-03-sycamore-canyon-in-february/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2008 14:35:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socalranch.land/posts/2008-03-03-sycamore-canyon-in-february/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have fond memories of learning to mountain bike at Sycamore. We visited Newbury Park last weekend so Hannah could get some time with her maternal grandparents and so Julie could see some of her girlfriends in the area. So on Friday afternoon I found myself with several hours to kill. Earlier I sent an email to a Newbury Park bike shop asking about any rental mountain bikes they might have but had not hear back from them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Luckily, my father-in-law has a rigid frame bike that looked like it was capable enough. After fiddling with the gears for a bit, trying to get the full range, i gave up and just made sure I had granny gear since I doubted I would be going full speed over the rough patches. I found an old helmet and off I went. I rode to the Wendy Dr trail head and started down. It was beautiful &amp;#8230; so green and sunny and the temperature was just right at 70. They must have gotten a lot of rain recently. I started on my usual warm up loop and found that they are now letting bikes go on the Hidden Pond trail. This started off good&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>